Hey. Um, look, I know
- 嗨 - 嗯，我知道
we've known each other for a really long time.
我们相识很久了
And we live across the street from each other and stuff.
住的也不远，还有…
And...
还有…
I know, like, in four days,
我知道，四天之后
I'm sure, if...
肯定，如果…
You know, prom's, like, in four days... Oh, my God.
- 你知道四天后，毕业舞会… - 哦，天啊
You're not asking me to prom, are you?
你不是邀请我当你舞伴吧？
Fuck, no.
妈的，不是
No, I... No, I just...
不是，不是…，我只是…
You're probably going with someone. I'm sorry.
- 你可能已经有舞伴了 - 对不起
I don't know how to put this nicely.
我不知道该怎么说好
There's not a nice way to put it.
怎么说都不好
You're a fucking nerd.
你就是个书呆子
And, you know... I don't know. She's hot.
你呢，我怎么说呢，她可是热门货
Look at her. Look at her.
看着她，看着她
Look at her. Look at her. Look at her. I'll see you later.
- 看着她啊，看着，看着 - 待会见
Bye. JENKO: All right, buddy, good talk.
- 再见 - 好啊，哥们，谈得不错
Dude, classic.
傻小子，经典
Greg Jenko to the principal's office. Greg Jenko to the principal's office.
格雷格・延科，请到校长办公室
Shit. Good luck, bro.
- 该死 - 兄弟好运
I said loud and clear,
我说得很清楚
if you didn't get your grades up, you weren't going to the prom.
如果你成绩上不去 就不能参加毕业舞会
You, my friend, are about to pay the piper.
我的朋友，后果你得自负
I should pay who?
付给谁？
You're not going to the prom.
毕业舞会没你的份
Boy, you lucky you even graduating.
孩子，你能毕业已经不错了
But I'm going to be prom king.
可我是舞会之王啊
I'm glad you had a great time in school.
不错，你在学校过得很开心
'Cause you ain't learned nothing.
因为你什么都不学
Fuck! Fuck!
靠！靠！
Welcome to the Police Academy.
警察学院欢迎你
Make sure your form is completely filled out, then move along.
先把表格填好 再说别的
Not-so-slim Shady, what's up? Holy shit!
是个不太苗条的娘们哈？我靠！
Jenko, Schmidt, you're up.
延科、施密特，你俩上
Oh, fuck!
啊，靠！
You're good at this, huh? Yeah, I am.
- 你摔跤很厉害哈？ - 没错
Thank you.
谢谢
Such bullshit.
真他妈的
You're really good at this.
你考试很厉害哈？
Yeah, I am.
没错
Hey, you want to be friends?
嗨，交个朋友？
Come on. Come on, let's go.
加油，加油，快跑
Come on, pick your knees up. Pick your knees up.
加油，膝盖上抬 抬膝
I'm telling you right now, it's not a felony.
我现在告诉你，这不是重罪
Chill, all right? Look, if it has intent, it's a felony.
冷静点，好不好？ 注意，如果是有意的，就是重罪
What did I tell you? Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go!
我早说过吧？ 起床，走了，走了！
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
加油，加油，加油，快跑
Faster. Let's go.
再快点，跑
Clear!
解除警戒！
- Come on, come on, come on! - Stop.
加油，加油，快！停
Yes! Yes!
好！好！
Let me see. Let me see.
让我看看，让我看看
Nice.
不错
Ten-hut! Ladies and gentlemen,
立正！女士们先生们
I present to you the graduates of Class 137.
我向大家介绍第137届毕业生
Get ready for a lifetime of being badass motherfuckers.
准备当一辈子混帐王八蛋吧
Oh, lam.
准备好了
I really thought this job would have more car chases and explosions,
我还以为当警察 会有很多爆炸，或飞车追逐之类的
and less homeless people doo-dooing everywhere.
可不是到处查看流浪汉 是否随地大小便
Do you guys really think this is a police matter?
你们觉得打捞飞盘
To get your Frisbee back?
是警察该干的吗？
Get your own fucking Frisbee.
你们他妈的自己捞去
Shit.
混蛋
Shit! Shit!
混蛋！混蛋！
Yours isn't loaded, right? Huh?
你枪里没装子弹吧？
We're supposed to unload them first, right?
我们应该先卸掉子弹，对吧？
What, you... No.
什么，你…不
That's no fun. Come on.
不是闹着玩的，真的
Sign says, "Do not feed the ducks."
牌子上写着"严禁喂鸭"
It's right there.
就在那
Don't you... Don't... Don't. Stop it.
- 你不许…不许 - 不可以，别这样
Don't. You did it. You fed the ducks.
不可以，你还是干了
You feel like a big shot?
觉得自己很牛？
No fucking way.
别想
One Percenters?
摩托帮？
These guys are, like, big-time drug dealers.
这些家伙可是大毒贩子
If we could take them down as our first bust, we'd be off park duty for sure.
如果我们第一次逮捕的是他们 肯定不用再做公园巡逻了
You see what I see?
你也看见了吧？
Cannabis sativa.
大麻
Chaka Khan.
准备登场
Chaka Khan?
登场？
Gentlemen. We having a little party?
先生们，在聚会吗？
Have we forgotten that the use of marijuana is illegal?
忘了抽大麻是违法的吗？
I have glaucoma.
我有青光眼
I get nervous in crowds.
人多我紧张
Herpes.
出疱疹
Then you won't mind if I search your bike, now, would you?
查一下你的自行车 不介意吧？
Go ahead. You won't find shit.
查吧，你屁也找不着
Clmate, gringo. Get up.
- 起来 - 冷静，美国佬
Man, you guys even real cops? You look like the kids on Halloween.
天，你们也算是警察？ 简直是万圣节孩子们装着玩的
If those boys is cops, I'm DEA.
这些娃娃要是警察 我就是缉毒局的了
I know, right? I know.
我知道，是吧？我知道
It's hilarious.
太可笑了
So why don't you show us a little respect?
放尊重点好吗？
Fuck you, pig- Hey.
- 操你妈，条子 - 嗨
You want me to beat your dick off?
想让我废了你？
You want to beat my dick off?
废了我？
I'll beat your dick off with both hands. What's up? Let's go.
两只手就能废了你 怎么样？试试
That's weird, man. SCHMIDT: I think what he was trying to say was,
- 不太可能吧 - 我想他的意思是
he's going to punch you so many times around the genital area
用拳头照你的生殖器部位连续猛击
that your dick's just going to fall off.
你那玩意就会掉下来
Why do you have salt in your...
怎么还带着盐…
That's actual drugs. Oh, my God.
- 那就是毒品 - 哦，天啊
Get on the ground! Hey!
趴地上！嗨！
- Come here now! - What do I do?
- 过来！ - 我怎么办？
- Chase someone! - Chase someone?
- 追一个！ - 追一个？
Are you leaving your bike here?
你不要车了？
Okay. All right.
好吧
Don't run from me! You're making it worse for yourself!
别跑！ 逃跑对你更不利！
No! Get out of the way!
嗨，闪开！
Stop!
站住！
I'm going to shoot you if you don't slow down, man! Come on!
你不站住，我要开枪了！ 听见了吗？
Hey! Come here!
嗨！站住！
I'm not playing any more! I'm so not kidding!
不陪你玩了！说正经的！
I got him. I got him.
这回看你往哪跑
Freeze! Freeze!
站住！不许动！
Hands up or I shoot you! Freeze!
举起手来 不然开枪了！站住！
That's it! Come here!
对！站住！
Freeze! Stop it!
不许动！站住！
You're a pussy!
真是个娘们！
You got the right to... Give me that! You got the right to...
你有权利…手过来！ 你有权利…
...to suck my dick, motherfucker!
…给我吹箫，你他妈的！
Oh, my elbow.
我的胳膊肘
You got nothing. How's my dick feel in your ass, huh?
- 你没证据 - 你那脏很爽吧？
Hey! Hey! How's it feel? How's it feel now?
- 嗨！嗨！ - 不错吧？感觉咋样？
That's right. Schmidt! Schmidt, we got one!
好了，施密特！我们抓住一个！
We got one! I got him!
抓住一个！逮住他了！
Yes! Yes!
太好了！
Yeah! We got an arrest!
- 好啊！ - 逮住一个！
Yeah! We got him! Yes!
- 好啊！逮住他了！ - 太棒了！
Yeah! Fuck you! Yeah! Fuck you! Yeah!
- 好啊！你他妈的！靠！ - 你他妈的！好啊！
What's up?
怎么着？
Drop my nuts on your motherfucking forehead!
把我的蛋蛋放在你他娘的脑门上！
That's right. Fuck you, park!
- 对 - 公园，我靠你！
We arrest people now! What up, park?
我们逮人了！ 公园怎么着？
What's up? What's up? What up, park? Who wants one?
- 咋样？咋样？ - 你们看什么？谁想来试试？
Congratulations on the bust, boys. It sounds great.
祝贺你们擒获歹徒，小伙子 真的很棒
- Thank you, Cinnamon. - Are those new?
谢谢，肉桂 新抓来的？
The department was forced to drop the charges
局里不得不取消控告
because you forgot to read him his Miranda rights.
因为你们忘了宣读米兰达警告
What possible reason is there for not doing the only thing
你们有什么正当理由 逮捕的时候
you have to do when arresting someone?
忘了做唯一应该做的事？
I did read him his right... I did a version of that.
我宣读了… 我读的是改版的
Do you even know the Miranda rights? Yes.
- 你究竟知道不知道米兰达警告？ - 知道
Let's hear them, then.
说来让我听听
You got a lot of stuff to do.
你还有很多事要做呢
No, go ahead. You going anywhere, Schmidt?
不不，说说 要去哪儿吗，施密特？
We got time.
不急
I had a thing, but I can probably push it back.
本来有事的，但可以推迟
Go ahead. It's four declamatory sentences, followed by a question,
说吧，只有四句话 外加一个问题
for a total of 57 words.
一共57个字
Okay. Look, it obviously starts with, "You have the right to remain silent."
好吧，开始是 "你有权利保持沉默"
I know you've heard this before. And then,
我知道你都听过的，然后是
I think it sounds something like...
我想，大概是…
"You have the right to an attorney." Well, the thing... Yeah, right.
- "你有权请律师" - 嗯，这…啊，对
"You have the right to remain an attorney."
"你有权留下律师"
Did you say that you have the right to be an attorney?
你是说 你有权利当律师？
You do have the right to be an attorney, if you want to.
如果愿意的话 你是有权利当律师的
Where were you?
当时你在哪？
I was chasing my perp, sir.
我在追赶罪犯，长官
And how did that go for you?
结果呢？
Honestly, he did get away,
诚实地讲，他逃了
and he threw me down pretty hard.
还把我摔得很惨
Actually fucked up my elbow pretty bad.
把我胳膊肘弄伤了
Can I see that?
我看看
Yeah, actually, it hurts 'cause the dirt gets mushed into it.
嗯，很疼 因为进去土了
Wow.
哇
Fortunately for you two,
你俩还算幸运
we're reviving a canceled undercover police program from the '80s
警察卧底计划80年代取消了 我们正在修改
and revamping it for modern times.
好适应现时的需要
You see, the guys in charge of this stuff
负责这件事的人
lack creativity and are completely out of ideas,
缺乏魄力 一点创意都没有
so all they do now is recycle shit from the past
他们只是 把以前的东西翻出来重新用
and expect us all not to notice.
还以为我们看不出来
One of these programs involves the use of young,
计划中有一项要用到
immature-seeming officers.
年轻的新警察
Sir, are you saying that you're going to send us into, like,
长官，你是说 要把我们送进
a child sex slavery ring or something?
儿童色情奴隶圈之类的地方？
Sir, if I have to suck somebody's dick, I will.
长官，如果需要我去吹箫 我会的
It's just... I'd prefer not to.
只是，我不喜欢
I think you idiots are perfect.
我觉得你们这些蠢货正合适
You're officially transferred.
你们已正式转调了
All right. Yeah. That's great.
- 好吧 - 好
Where should we report to?
我们的上司是谁？
Down on Jump Street.
到跳跳街去
37 Jump Street.
跳跳街37号
No, that doesn't sound right.
好像号码不对
Is it...
是…
This has got to be a joke.
这玩笑开大了
This is it.
就是这
Aroma of Christ Church?
芬芳基督堂？
How's it going?
你们好
This place is weird.
这地方怪怪的
Everybody comfortable?
大家都还好吧？
Yeah.
好
Get your motherfucking ass up when I'm talking!
我说话时 都他妈的给我站起来听！
You will be going undercover as high school students.
你们都要当高中生去卧底
You are here simply because you look young.
选你们来是因为你们长得年轻
You some Justin Beaver,
跟超级小天王贾斯汀比伯
Miley Cyrus-looking motherfuckers.
和小天后麦莉赛勒斯一样嫩
Captain Sassy.
粗暴队长
I know what you're thinking,
我知道你们会说我
"Angry Black Captain."
是"暴躁的黑队长"
It ain't nothing but a stupid stereotype.
这是愚蠢的无稽之谈
Well, guess what, motherfuckers.
知道吗，混帐
I'm black.
我是黑人
And I worked my ass off to be the captain!
我拼了老命才当上队长！
And sometimes I get angry.
有时我真的生气
So suck a dick!
去他妈的！
What I'm trying to show you is,
我想让你们明白的是
embrace your stereotypes.
拥抱你们的无稽之谈
Like this guy right here. Handsome.
就像这个家伙，帅呆了
And he's probably a dummy.
但可能是个傀儡
And then this guy.
再看这位
He's short and insecure.
个子矮，没主心骨
And he's probably good with money.
不过可能会理财
You are good with money. What the fuck?
- 你会理财 - 哪对哪啊？
Didn't somebody tell you guys this was an undercover unit?
没人告诉过你们 这里是卧底部？
I don't... I actually didn't...
我没…其实我没…
I didn't get a letter or anything.
没收到调动函
Yeah, like, a start time... With a dress code or anything like that.
- 对，没说从什么时候开始 - 穿什么之类的事
Teenage the fuck up!
你是他妈的青少年！
Rule number one at Jump Street. Fugazy.
跳跳街规则第一条 付嘉曦
Do not get expelled.
不要被学校开除
Nobody in the system knows you're here. All right? Nobody.
整个系统没人知道你们在这 知道吗？谁都不知道
You get kicked out of school,
如果你被学校开除了
your monkey ass is getting kicked out of Jump Street.
也等于被跳跳街踢出去了
Rule number two Burns.
第二条，彭司
Do not have sexual relations with students or teachers, sir.
严禁与学生或教师发生性关系，长官
You hear that? That's you.
听见了？说你呢
Don't do it, man. Why...
- 不允许 - 为什么…
Keep that dirty dick in your pants. Dirty?
- 把你那脏兮兮的玩意放裤档里 - 脏兮兮？
Don't fuck no students.
不许跟学生上床
Don't fuck no teachers.
也不许跟老师
Sir, I know we come off as a couple of lady-killers,
长官，我知道虽然我们俩 帅得出了名
but I promise you we will be super professional on the job.
但我保证，工作起来 绝对有职业操守
Clearly, I wasn't talking to you, Big Titties.
我没跟你说话，大波波
You cherub-looking motherfucker.
你这娃娃脸蛋的混蛋
I was talking to your partner over here.
我跟你搭档说话呢
Fake-ass Handsome McGee.
装了假屁股的帅哥麦吉
When I'm talking to him, I'm talking to him.
我跟他说话就是跟他说
When I say, "Shut the fuck up,"
我说"闭上鸟嘴"
I'm talking to you. Cool.
- 才是跟你说话 - 酷
Now, you two sons of bitches, in my office now.
你俩个妹子养的 立刻到我办公室去
Right now!
马上！
Hi. I am Billiam Willingham.
你好，我是彼廉威灵翰
So I bought these,
我买了这个
which is all anybody seems to be talking about right now.
现在好像人人在都谈论这东西
Cheers.
来一口
It's a new synthetic drug.
这是一种合成毒品
Goes by the street name H.F.S.
大街上流行的名字是H.F.S.
Holy fucking shit.
真他妈爽
Holy...
真他妈…
They put this on the Internet for everybody to see?
他们把这东西放到网上 让大家看？
They're teenagers, man. They're really stupid.
他们是青少年 一帮蠢货
So you should blend right in.
所以你们得赶快混进去
Jessica, will you go to prom with me? But I already know the answer. It's yes.
杰西卡，毕业舞会给我当舞伴行吗？ 不过我知道你已经答应了
I could watch this kid all day.
这孩子，我能看一天
Man, this kid rules.
天，这孩子真行
Ruled.
曾经行
His parents found him OD'd in his room a few days ago.
几天前父母 在他房间发现他吸毒过量
He's dead.
死了
Whatever he took, the lab has never seen it before.
他用的这种毒品 实验室从没见过
And as you can see, this kid is white.
而且，你也看得出来，他是白人
That means people actually give a shit.
我的意思是，他有家庭的关怀
Sir, I just want to throw out to you that I would give a shit if he was black.
长官，我只想说 即使他是黑孩子，我也会关怀他
Right now, H.F.S. is contained right there at Sagan High.
现在H.F.S.已经在萨根高中范围内得到遏制
Now, once this drug breaks containment, it goes viral in a few days.
一旦这种毒品突破遏制 几天之内就会泛滥开来
Jenko, I looked at your old transcript.
延科，我看了你以前的成绩单
I enrolled you in a bunch of bullshit courses
我给你随便选了几门课
like photography and drama.
摄影、戏剧之类的
Get in with the burnouts and the cool kids.
跟那些辍学的、吸毒的混熟
Find out who's slinging this shit.
看看谁在贩卖这种毒品
Schmidt, says you were a virgin
施密特，据说你高中时
through high school. It says that?
- 一直是处男 - 真的？
No. I just assumed it,
不是，我只是假设
due to your many years on the honor roll and your membership to the juggling squad.
因为好多年你都是优等生 而且还是杂耍队的
It's the Juggling Society, but it's fine. It's fine.
是杂耍学会，没什么，无所谓
They're stealing equipment from the chemistry lab.
他们偷化学实验室的仪器
That's what we think they're cooking the dope with.
我们认为是去弄熟毒品
I enrolled you into honors chemistry.
我给你在化学高班报了名
Here's your new identities, all right?
这是你们的新身份，明白吗？
Brad and Doug McQuaid.
布莱德和道格・麦奎德
The mission is this.
任务是
Infiltrate the dealers, find the supplier.
打入毒品贩内部，找出供货商
We get to be brothers?
我们是哥俩？
But if we find the supplier first, we don't have to worry about the dealers.
先找到供货商 就不必再去费劲找毒贩子了
God damn. Infiltrate the dealers, find the supplier.
该死的 打入毒品贩内部，找出供货商
Hey, Korean Jesus.
嗨，韩人耶稣
I don't know if you only cater to Korean Christians
不知道你是不是只照顾韩人基督徒
or if you even exist. No offense.
也许你根本不存在，别见怪啊
I just...
只是…
I'm really freaked out about going back to high school.
要回到高中上学 我好害怕
It was just so fucking hard the first time.
因为上次就他妈的不好过
I know we haven't made our first arrest, or maybe I'm not the best cop.
我知道至今我们还一个人都没逮捕过 也许我不是最棒的警察
Korean Jesus, I just really don't want to fuck this up.
韩人耶稣 这次我他妈真不想把事情搞砸
I'm sorry for swearing so much.
我满嘴脏话，很抱歉
The end?
最后？
I don't really know how to end a prayer. The end?
我真不知道该怎么结束祷告 最后？
Yeah.
对
Hey! Hey!
嗨！嗨！
Stop fucking with Korean Jesus!
别他妈亵渎韩人耶稣！
He ain't got time for your problems. He busy!
他没时间给你解决问题，他忙着呢！
With Korean shit.
忙韩国的事
You two get to your mama house ASAP. What?
- 你们俩赶快回家找妈妈去 - 什么？
You're teenagers now, all right?
你们现在是青少年，明白吗？
You two are staying at Schmidt's parents' house
执行这个任务期间 你们俩
for the duration of this assignment.
住在施密特父母家
Oh, fuck me.
妈的，惨了
This house is adorable.
这房子挺可爱
My baby's home! Come here.
我的宝贝回家了，来来
You will always be my infant angel baby child.
你永远都是我的天使宝贝
There's my guy.
好孩子
It's great to see you guys.
很高兴见到你们
Hey. Schmidt family! Up top, Papa Schmidt.
- 嗨 - 施密特家！手举起来，施密特爸爸
Oh, my God. Mama Schmidt, did you do all this yourself?
啊，天啊 施密特妈妈，都是你自己做的？
This is unbelievable. Well, yeah.
- 简直不可思议 - 是啊
I guess I did. It's gorgeous!
- 是我做的 - 太棒了！
So are you.
你也很棒
Honey, listen, I want to tell you, we did blow up the air mattress in your room
宝贝，我跟你说 我们在你房间放了气垫
'cause we're kind of using that as a workout area,
那里成了健身房
so I hope you don't mind the elliptical.
有个椭圆机，你别介意
No, no! Jenko, Jenko, oh, my God, please. No, no.
别，别！延科，天，可别
Don't touch that. We just brought it back from Sedona.
别碰那东西 我们刚从赛多纳买来的
Guys, can we get rid of this stuff?
我说，我们能不能扔掉这些？
I mean, it looks like I died in a car crash
感觉像我出车祸死了
and you guys haven't moved on. Rid of it?
- 你们从此沉浸在回忆中 - 拿掉？
If we take it down, we have to stop bragging about you.
拿下来的话 我们就没法吹你了
I look like Fred Savage from The Wonder Years,
我就像The Wonder Years里的弗莱德萨维奇
but completely naked, wearing Indian friendship bracelets.
只不过赤身裸体 还戴着印第安人的友谊手链
That is a great picture, Morton. Mmm-hmm.
莫顿，这张照片很棒的
You look like a young Jay Leno.
很像杰雷诺年轻时候
Am I even wearing underwear in this picture?
照这张相的时候，我穿内裤了吗？
No.
没穿
I remember. You know why?
我记得，知道为啥吗？
Because I've told it to a therapist about 8,000 times.
因为我曾经跟一位理疗师 讲过8000遍
I mean, this is a fourth grade
我是说，这个奖章是四年级 因为参加足球比赛得的
participation medal for soccer.
努力奖
It's literally a medal for sucking.
意思是踢得太差了
No, that is a medal for trying. Yes.
- 不，这是奖励你努力尝试 - 对
Let me tell you something. This guy was always a great tryer.
我跟你说 这孩子总是很努力的
That must be Phyllis. She is just dying to see you.
一定是菲利斯 她很想见你
What? Mom, you told Phyllis I was here? She's going to tell the whole neighborhood.
什么？妈，我回家你告诉菲利斯了？ 她会让街坊邻居都知道的
I told you, it's an undercover assignment. It's super secretive.
告诉过你，这是卧底任务 绝密的
"Undercover." That's so cute.
"卧底"，真可爱
I'm going upstairs. Okay, honey. I want you to know
- 我要上楼了 - 好吧，宝贝，你要知道
we are so glad you're here. Okay.
- 你回来我们好高兴 - 好
That's great. Thank you.
很好，谢谢
All right. Where is he? He's upstairs.
- 好吧，他在哪？ - 在楼上
He just needs to take a little rest, and then he's dying to see you, too.
他需要休息一会 他也很想见你
Bye-bye. I baked muffins!
- 再见 - 我烤了小松糕！
If you don't know your identity, we're screwed tomorrow.
你要是不知道自己的身份 明天非乱套不可
You got to study this stuff.
好好看看这个
Forget those identities. They're bullshit. They said I was held back a year.
别理它，身份都是胡扯 他们说我留级一年
You were. You were held back two years.
本来就是，留过两年呢
Just 'cause it's a fake backstory doesn't mean it doesn't hurt my feelings.
虽然背景故事是编的 也照样让我伤心
Fuck! Socks don't match.
妈的！两只袜子不一样
I got to start all over.
还得从头开始
It's the first day of school, dude. I got to look awesome.
第一天去学校 我要很精神
You know, back in the day, you were super popular,
那个时候，你红得发紫
and I wasn't as much.
我比你差远了
We didn't really get along in high school.
其实，高中时我们合不来
You don't think that's going to happen again, do you?
这次不会再这样了吧？
No. Come on, man. We're adults now. We're best buds.
不会，嗨，哥们，我们都是成年人了 是最要好的朋友
It's definitely not going to happen again.
绝不会再像以前了
We're good. Cool.
- 我们挺好的 - 酷
Beautiful day out there, boys.
外面天气很好啊，孩子们
Just shut up.
闭嘴吧
"Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law."
"你所说的一切 都可能用作法庭控告你的证据
"You have the right to an attorney."
"你有权利请律师
"If you cannot afford an attorney, one will be appointed..."
"如果你付不起律师费 法庭会为你…"
Dude, do you still not know the Miranda rights? You're a cop.
小子，你还记不住米兰达警告？ 你可是个警察啊
Come on, man. They always cutaway on TV before they finish them.
得了，电视上从来没说过完整的
All right, let's do it.
好吧，咱们开工吧
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What?
- 咳，咳，咳 - 怎么了？
What are you doing?
这是干嘛？
What? What are you talking about? Are you two-strapping?
- 怎么了？啥意思？ - 你双肩背包？
My backpack? Yeah. Yeah, I got to be seen with you.
- 书包？是啊 - 好，我们俩得一致
You got to one-strap it.
你得单肩背
Seriously, I would no-strap it if that would even be possible.
真的，如果可能的话 我连包都不背
Okay, what makes you the expert?
好吧，你怎么这么懂行？
I was cool in high school, and you weren't.
我在高中很酷，不像你
Okay, that makes sense. Continue.
好吧，你有理，走吧
The Three Keys of Coolness in High School, by Jenko.
延科高中扮酷三秘诀
One, don't try hard at anything.
一，不要事事都努力
Okay? Two, make fun of people who do try.
明白吗？二，嘲笑那些努力的人
Three, be handsome.
三，要帅
Four, if anyone steps to you on the first day of school,
四，如果上学第一天有人威胁你
you punch them directly in the face.
就迎面给他一拳
Five, drive a kick-ass car.
五，开一辆奇车
Shit.
妈的
All right, but just don't be driving it like teenagers,
好，但别像小年轻的那样开
revving up the engine and shit, okay?
使劲轰轰引擎，好吗？
We would never.
不会的
Come on, Hoffs. Give us a little credit.
哎呀，朱迪，你要相信我们
Hey, you ready? Go!
- 嗨，准备好了吗？ - 开始！
That was awesome! That was amazing.
太棒了！绝了
Was I flying? That was amazing.
- 我飞起来了？ - 太棒了
All right, do mine, do mine.
好，该我了，该我了
Okay, ready? Here I go. Yeah, yeah.
- 好，准备好了？开始 - 好
You Okay?
你没事吧
I think I shit my pants.
我也许吓尿裤了
Hey, park in that handicapped spot.
停在残疾人车位
It'll make us look cool. That's awesome.
- 我们这样显得很酷 - 太棒了
Dude?
小子
Everybody's two-strapping it. Just stay with the one-strap.
- 大伙都双肩背呢 - 你别改
I can't. I can't. I can't right now.
不行，我得改过来
What are you doing? What are you doing? Don't succumb to the peer pressure.
那干嘛？干什么？ 别让群体压力影响你
What are you doing? You're supposed to use two straps.
- 干嘛？ - 我们应该双肩背
One strap is peer pressure. No. No. You're fucking up right now.
- 单肩背才是压力 - 不不，你简直是乱来
Okay, those are Goths.
看，那帮人是黑白哥特派
Those are nerds.
那些是书呆子
I don't know what they are.
不知道这些人是什么
What the fuck are those things?
这些人是他妈什么呢？
I'm so confused right now.
我现在发懵
Whoa.
哇
Hi. Hey.
- 嗨 - 嗨
Hey. Good morning.
- 嗨 - 早上好
Hey, yo. Hey.
嗨，嗨
Is that your car? Yeah.
- 你的车？ - 没错
What's that thing get, 10 miles to the gallon?
一升油只跑16公里吧
No, try, like, seven.
不，也就10公里吧
What about you? Biodiesel, dawg.
- 你的呢？ - 生物柴油的，哥们
Smells like egg rolls.
味道像蛋卷
Yeah, it does. Runs on leftover fry oil from Hunan Palace.
没错 燃料是湖南餐厅炸东西剩下的油
But we try to ride bikes when we can. Global crisis and whatnot.
但我们还是尽量骑自行车 全球性危机什么的
Whatever, man. I don't care about anything.
管他什么，我反正无所谓
You don't care about the environment? That's kind of fucked up, man.
对环境无所谓？ 你真他妈够呛
Hey, hey, will y'all shut the hell up?
嗨嗨，都闭嘴行不行？
I'm trying to study. Thanks.
我想看书，谢谢
Look at him. He's trying.
瞧啊，他想
He's actually trying. What a nerd.
他真的想，呆子
Look at the nerd. Look at the nerd.
瞧这个呆子，瞧啊
Look at him. Look at the nerd. Who you calling a nerd, man?
- 瞧啊，瞧这个呆子 - 你说谁是呆子？
I'm sorry. What...
对不起，来个…
Shit! Shit, dude.
- 妈的 - 妈的，小子
Are you okay, man? Hey, what the hell? Are you serious?
你没事吧？太过分了吧？ 真打啊？
Well, turn that gay-ass music off.
把你那同志音乐关了
You punched me because I'm gay? What?
- 你揍我因为我是同志？ - 什么？
No. Oh, Come on.
不是，好家伙
That's not cool, man.
这可不酷
That is really insensitive.
你真迟钝
I didn't punch him because he's gay.
不是因为他是同志揍他
I punched him, and then he happened to turn out to be gay afterwards.
我揍了他之后才发现原来他是同志
I was gay when you punched me! In a weird way,
- 你揍我时我已经是同志了 - 奇怪
it might have been homophobic not to punch you
如果因为你是同志 他就不敢揍你的话
just because you were gay. Right.
- 那就是同性恋恐惧症 - 对
You punched a little gay black kid in the face,
才上了一节课 就用拳头
and it's not even second period. How do you explain that?
揍了一个黑人小同志的脸 你怎么解释？
Mr. Dadier, I'm so sorry about that. I just...
迭喋先生，我很抱歉，我只是…
Look, guys, I'm going to relate to you, okay?
听着，说点跟你们有关的
A kid died the other day from drugs,
那天有个孩子吸毒过量，死了
and nobody, including me, is doing anything about it.
没人，包括我在内 敢有任何作为
That's weird, guys.
很奇怪吧
And then you two show up, with 30 days left,
还剩30天 你们俩来了
causing trouble in my school.
就在学校里闹事
I am one more black gay kid getting punched in the face
再有一个黑人同性恋被揍
away from a nervous breakdown. Do I make myself clear?
我就精神崩溃了 明白了吗？
You guys cross my line again,
如果你们再犯
and you walk into this office, I'm going to expel you. You got me?
再走进这间办公室 我就开除你们，明白了吗？
All right, let's do this. Which one of you is Doug?
来吧，你们俩谁是道格？
Let's do that again and pretend you guys aren't weird.
把你们俩当正常人 我再问一次
Which one of you is named Doug?
谁是道格？
No, dude, I'm Brad. Okay, good.
- 傻瓜，我是布莱德 - 好啊
So that means your name is Doug, son.
这么说你是道格了，孩子
Yeah, I'm Doug. Great.
- 对，我是道格 - 好
Here are your class schedules.
这是你们的课程表
Funny, I wouldn't have taken you for the brainy type.
奇怪，我也不想测你们的智力类型了
I wouldn't. But you as a drama geek, far less surprising.
我不测了 但你爱好戏剧，也没什么奇怪的
Thank you.
谢谢
Now we have the wrong identities, you dumb-ass.
我们把身份搞混了 你个笨蛋
I'm in drama. I suck at drama. It's girly and embarrassing.
戏剧课，我最不行了 都是女孩子的玩意，太让人为难了
Oh, my God. Relax, dude. Who cares?
上帝啊，放轻松些，谁在乎啊？
I can fake my way through band practice and app chemistry for a few weeks.
乐队练习和大学先求化学课 我还能装装，对付几周
AP Chemistry. AP Chemistry. And, no, you can't,
先修化学，先修 天，你装不了
because you don't even know what it's actually fucking called!
连课程名称你他妈都不知道
It's going to be fine. You go to my classes, and I'm going to go to yours.
没事的 你上我的课，我上你的
Okay, now, chemistry's the one with the shapes and shit, right?
对了，化学说的是 形状什么的，对吧？
Fuck.
妈的
So, we are going to hold auditions for the Peter Pan part today.
今天，我们为《彼得潘》做试听选拔
Billiam would've wanted the show to go on.
彼廉一定希望《彼得潘》能演下去
When I was a young actor just starting out in New York state,
我年轻时 刚在纽约州当演员那会
Albany, to be exact,
确切地说，是奥尔巴尼
I booked a local television commercial... Hey.
- 我签了当地电视广告的约 - 嗨
...In which I had to play a young man...
…扮演一个年轻人…
It's really sad about that kid. He was talented.
那孩子真倒霉，他满有天赋的
So are you saying if he wasn't talented, it would be less sad?
你是说，如果他没什么天赋 就不那么倒霉了？
No. No, no, no, that's not what I meant.
不不不，我不是那意思
I was just busting your balls.
我逗你蛋蛋呢
Okay. Good.
哦，好
I remember, one time, doing cocaine with Willie Nelson's horse,
我记得有一次 我跟威利尼尔森的马玩可卡因
and we were having so much fun.
我们玩得很高兴
And then I realized that she was dead.
后来发现，它死了
I remember one summer...
记得一年夏天
Do kids still do this stuff?
那个彼廉死了以后
Even after what happened to him?
孩子们还这么干？
Everyone's saying that Billiam had a heart murmur.
大伙都说 彼廉心脏本来就有杂音
Pretty much everyone I know does it, but it's not my thing.
我认识的人差不多都吸 但不关我的事
It's not really my thing, either,
我也一样
but a buddy of mine really wants it.
可我的一个哥们特想要
Who would he call if he wanted it?
他想要的话，给谁打电话？
Well, you can tell your friend
也许你可以告诉你朋友
that if he really wanted it,
如果他真的想要
it's not so hard to find.
其实找到并不难
When to take it. He shouldn't have been taking it at all.
什么时候吸最好 你根本就不应该吸
Drugs are bad.
毒品有害
But they can have their place in the life of a professional actor.
但是他们在职业演员的 演艺生涯中占有一席之位
Thank you. Oh, you're welcome.
- 谢谢你 - 不客气
Notice the distinction. I said "professional actor."
注意区别 我说的是"职业演员"
New person. Mr. Texty Texty.
新来的，短信先生
Since you have so much to say to Molly,
既然你跟莫莉有那么多话要说
let's see if you can be Peter to our Wendy.
我们看看你能不能扮演彼得 和剧中的温迪配戏
You look like you might have a little Peter inside of you.
你看着也许有点彼得的性格
Uh, I can't. I'm fine just being a tree or something.
我不行 我当颗树之类的，也许还行
Doug, you never won't know
道格，你还没做
what you can't achieve before you don't achieve it.
怎么能知道你不能做到
My point is,
我的意思是
you have to. Everyone auditions for Peter.
你必须做，每个人都要试试
Yeah, sure.
好吧
My favorite molecule is water.
水分子啊我最爱
I'd marry it, unless it was my daughter.
作我女友娶回来
Its solid form floats on its liquid form, which makes it far outside the norm.
固体浮于液体上 它有多么不寻常
It allowed life to form on ancient Mars, and we use it to wash our cars.
古时火星造生命 用它把车洗干净
H2O.
一氧化二氢
H2O It's okay. Thank you.
- 一氧化二氢 - 好了，谢谢
Thank you, Zack. Whoo! So good.
谢谢你扎克，真棒
All right, anybody else for Molecule Mondays? Anyone?
还有谁来展示一下"分子星期一"？
Okay. Time for a pop Quiznos.
好，我们做抽查小测验
A What?
小什么？
Oh, I'm sorry.
对不起
What is your name? Brad?
你叫什么？布莱德？
Brad. Yes, ma'am. Wow. Look at you,
- 布莱德，老师 - 哇，这名字
Brad. Big.
布，广布的布
What is a pop Quiznos?
抽查小测验是什么呢
It's a quiz, and the first person who finishes gets a $10 gift certificate to Quiznos.
是一个小测验，最先做完的 获得奎滋餐厅的10块钱礼券
Today's quiz is on... You look really old.
- 今天的题目是… - 你看着很大
Were you held back or something or... No. You look super young.
- 你留级了还是… - 没有，你看着很小
Were you held forward?
跳级了？
I went to school in France, so...
我在法国上的学，所以…
And they do, like, two extra years of middle school there. It's so lame.
他们中学比这里多两年 多无聊
French, the language of love.
法语，爱的语言
That's cool, man. It's nice to meet you also.
真酷，哥们，很高兴认识你
Hey.
嗨
Good luck.
好运
กำ I've gotta crow
我有只乌鸦
กำ I'm just the cleverest... กำ
我是聪明绝顶的…
Okay.
停
Maybe try one cooler.
要不，找一首更酷的试试？
And faster.
快一点的
And louder. And better.
大点声，唱好点
And less insecure and more just cool.
更有信心，更酷
Okay, yeah, those are great notes.
这样，这歌挺好
I'm going to run outside,
我得出去一下
and I'm going to utilize those, and I'm going to come back.
我要好好唱这首歌 我会回来的
It's such bullshit.
纯粹胡扯
Wow. You're fast.
哇，你好快
Not like that. Just, let me check you out.
交卷快不算数 我得看一下
Let me check out your chest.
看看你大腿
Check out your test... Let me...
哦，看你答对…多少
Let me grade your quiz.
等我来评分
Um, can I go take a dump?
我去大便行吗？
Yeah, okay. That's cool.
可以，真酷
Oh. We have this "hurry back" rule,
我们有"速回"规定
so if you're not back in six minutes, I have to send you to the principal.
6分钟回不来 我就得让你去见校长
Rules are rules, so,
规定不能违反
I guess this will have to be a quickie.
你得快点办大事
Which way is yearbook? I don't know.
- 年鉴室在哪？ - 不知道
Is it this way? I don't know!
- 这边？ - 不知道！
Yo. Hey.
- 嗨 - 嗨
You guys, huh?
你们啊？
That was a total mix-up, what happened earlier.
今天早晨的事 纯粹是误会
Yeah. He feels awful. He feels...
- 是啊 - 他很内疚，很…
Totally, very nervous.
绝对，特不安
You're the dealer?
你是贩子？
You're the dealer guy? Is that you?
- 你？ - 是你？
Yep.
是
So do you make the stuff or...
自己做的还是…
Do I look like a fucking scientist? No, I just sell it.
我看着像他妈的科学家吗？ 不，我只管卖
Yeah, he just sells it Come on. Yeah, no, I'm sorry.
- 哦，他只管卖 - 哦，抱歉
I meant I just... How many you guys want?
- 我是说… - 你们想要多少？
20 bucks a pop.
20块一份
One each? One pop each of drugs.
一份？就一份？
You guys aren't narcs, are you?
不是缉毒的吧？
Whoa!
咳！
Dude, come on. No! Maybe you're a narc.
- 小子，说啥呢 - 没准你是
You know who calls people narcs?
知道什么人把缉毒的叫特警吗？
Narcs, narc.
缉毒探子
First of all, your argument kind of just collapsed on itself,
你的说法首先就不成立
because if you call us narcs,
你要是把我们叫探子
if narcs call people narcs, and you call us narcs, then that's kind of...
而探子也说别人是探子 你说我们是探子，这有点…
'Cause you just said that. They call people...
- 因为你刚才说的 - 他们说…
Look, I don't have time for this shit. You guys want to do this or not?
听着，没时间听你们废话 你们到底要不要？
Jesus. Yes.
- 天 - 要
Yes, yes. No problem.
- 要，要 - 没问题
All right, take it here so I know you're cool.
好吧，在这吃，证明你们真的酷
I'm sorry. What?
啊？什么？
We were going to take it home. I gotta go back to class,
- 我们想带回家的 - 我还得回教室呢
is the only thing. I was thinking that I was going to go home,
- 很麻烦的 - 我是想回家吃的时候
maybe turn down the lights,
把灯光调暗
getting snuggy, get a little weird.
舒舒服服地爽一下
I was going to take it, and then masturbate later.
我是想吃了以后 噜噜管
Okay, I'm not asking. Take it now or get the fuck out.
我没让你干 现在吃，要不就滚蛋
I got to finish the girls' volleyball page by lunch.
午饭前我得把女子排球队页面弄完
Yeah?
行吗？
Yeah, no, it's all good.
行，没问题
I love doing drugs at school. I'll just take the drugs right here,
- 我喜欢在学校吃 - 我从这里打开
in our mouths.
放嘴里
There you go. That's it.
对，就这样
What is that? Barbecue? Cool Ranch?
这是什么口味？烧烤型还是清凉型？
Have fun.
爽去吧
You got to pull the trigger! Okay.
- 得用手指勾 - 好
You got to pull the trigger!
用手指勾出来
We got to throw up, man. I can't.
- 你得吐出来 - 吐不出来
We gotta throw up. That kid, Billiam, died. We got to throw up.
一定要吐，彼廉就死了 必须吐出来
Just think of something gross. Think of something gross.
想想恶心的事 让你想吐的
You fucking think of something. Okay, all right, all right.
- 你他妈快想点恶心的 - 好吧，好吧
Your grandma's vagina, and there's a dick going into it.
你奶奶的穴里有个
What the fuck are you saying? I don't know! I'm just trying!
你他妈说啥呢？ 不知道，帮你嘛
I'm trying my best! I'm just trying! Fuck! Come on, man!
- 我想帮你嘛！ - 靠！快！
Dude, let's just finger each other's mouths.
咱们互相用手指勾
No! Yeah.
不！ 来吧
No, you're not fingering my mouth.
你手指不能进我嘴
Do you wanna die? Do you wanna die? Okay, fine!
- 你想死吗？想死吗？ - 好吧！
Let's go. Come on. Come on! Come on!
来吧，来！
What are you doing? Are you trying to find my G-spot?
你干嘛呢？ 找我的G点啊？
Just stick it in! I don't know. I've never done this before!
- 伸进去！ - 不知道，没干过！
Just stick it in! Go!
捅进去！捅！
Cut your fucking fingernails!
你他妈指甲太长了！
Oh, God!
天！
Is it me?
是我吗？
I'm sorry.
对不起
I just can't sometimes.
我吐不出来
Think we're going to be fine. I don't feel anything.
我想我们没事 我一点感觉都没有
Me, neither.
我也是
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
咳，咳，咳！
You got a pass for running around the hallways like a couple of ding-a-lings?
你们俩在楼道里 疯子似的乱跑，有许可证吗？
Pass, in your hand.
在你手里呢
Hello.
哈
Oh, damn. You guys are late.
该死，你们俩迟到了
Now I'm going to have to take you to the principal's office.
我得把你们交给校长办公室
No, no, no, man. Come on, please. Sorry. Come on, please.
- 别别别，求你了，对不起 - 求你了
You have exceptional muscle tone there, young man.
你肌肉真棒啊 年轻人
When'd you go through puberty? Like, at seven or something?
你什么时候开始发育的？ 7、8岁？
You look like you're in your mid-20s, for crying out loud.
你看着像20几岁的 搞什么名堂
McQuaid, huh? Doug McQuaid.
麦奎德？道格・麦奎德
I read your file.
我看了你档案
You got a lot of something special going on there, young man.
你确实很特别哈，小伙子
What the hell was that? God damn it, son!
那是干什么？见鬼，小崽子！
Don't ever raise your hand to me like that again, all right?
别再那样举手，行不行？
I consider that a threat.
我以为是威胁
I was just saying that I'm Doug.
我是说我才是道格
I'm Doug McQuaid. See, that's Brad.
我是道格・麦奎德，他是布莱德
That's Brad.
他是布莱德
You're the new kid who's All County in track?
你是新来的那个 全郡最棒的田径选手？
Yes, I'm Doug McQuaid,
是，道格・麦奎德
the track star, and this is Brad, the science prodigy.
田径明星，这位是布莱德 理科天才
He's really fast.
他真的很快
Is this funny to you guys?
可笑吗？
So you're Doug.
那，你是道格，你是道格，你是道格
You're Doug. You're Doug.
你是道格，你是道格
Here's the deal.
这样吧
My track team is full of physically incapable rejects.
我们田径队 尽是些体能残废
I mean, if I wasn't the coach, I'd be laughing my ass off
我是说，如果我是教练 看到他们那笨样子
at how spastic they are, but I am the coach,
会笑掉大牙 可我还就是教练
so I need you.
所以我需要你
I need me some Doug McQuaid.
我叫道格・麦奎德
Understand?
明白吗？
I need you to run anchor on the 4 X 400 at today's track meet.
我需要你在今天运动会上 跑接力的最后一棒
You do that, and I'll sign this pass.
你答应的话，我就给你在许可证上签字
Don't blow on me, son.
别让我丢脸
I haven't trained.
我没训练过
Guys, don't make me take you to the principal's office.
你们不愿意去校长办公室吧
Do we have a deal?
说好的，对吧？
Yes.
对
Nice.
好
I don't like that. Put your tongue back in your mouth.
我不喜欢那样子 把舌头放回嘴里
Put your tongue in your mouth, and close it.
放回嘴里，闭上
What are you doing? Stop it.
你干嘛？别这样
Actually, that's not bad.
倒也不难看
All right, here you go.
好吧，给你
Are you guys on drugs?
你们吸毒了？
Okay.
好
One particle of Unobtainium has a nuclear reaction with a flux capacitor.
稀有矿物的一个微粒 与通量电容器发生核反应
Carry the two, changing its atomic isotoner into a radioactive spider.
这里进位，把原子的 等中子异位素改变为放射性蜘蛛人
Fuck you, science!
物理，去你妈的！
All right, all right, we're good. Whoo!
好了，好了，我们好了
We're good. We're good, man. We're good.
我们好了，好了，我们好了
We're good, baby. Whoo!
我们好了，宝贝
Good work. Hit that shit.
干得好，弹前奏
กำ I've gotta crow
我有只乌鸦
กำ I'm just the cleverest fellow
我是聪明绝顶的娃
กำ 'Twas ever my fortune to know
这等幸运我无法表达
กำ I taught a trick to my shadow
我教会影子变戏法
กำ To stick to the tip of my toe
让它不离我的脚丫
กำ I've gotta crow
我有只乌鸦
กำ I've gotta
我有只
กำ Crow! กำ
乌鸦
Christoph, did you feel that?
克里斯托弗，有感觉吗？
Who are you?
你是谁？
Welcome aboard, Peter.
欢迎加入，彼得
Whoo! No, keep it going!
别停，继续！
Keep it going. That was so tight!
继续，刚才很紧凑
No, no, no, keep it going. Keep it going.
不不，继续，继续
All right, let's go, McQuaid!
好啦，开始，麦奎德！
All right! Yeah!
好！没问题！
I like it! I like the confidence, son!
我喜欢，喜欢你这种自信！
I know y'all seen this shit before. I know you've seen this shit before.
我知道你们都看过这个
Huge lead! Huge lead! We got this. All right.
远远领先！远远领先！我们能赢，好的
You're looking amped!
你好兴奋
Here we go.
他来了
Here we go! Here we go!
他来了！来了！
Hey, pick it up!
嗨，加速！
Hey, no, McQuaid, pick it up. What are you doing?
嗨，麦奎德，加速啊 你在干嘛？
What are you doing? Pick it...
干嘛呢？加…
What? McQuaid!
啊？麦奎德！
Don't throw the baton, you jackass!
别扔接力棒啊，你个蠢货！
Come on!
天啊！
McQuaid!
麦奎德！
Run that way!
往那边跑！
Spike that! Fuck you, Miles Davis!
去你妈的迈尔斯・戴维斯！
Let's go, God damn it! Let's do this!
来啊，奶奶的，咱们继续练！
Let's go! Come on!
练啊，练起来！
Oh, my God.
噢，天啊
No, no.
不不
No, stop.
别这样
Come here. Come here.
过来，过来
Don't make a...
别拿它当…
That is a baton penis.
接力棒阳物
Oh, speak of the devil!
说曹操，曹操到！
Dude, that was awesome how you sabotaged that track meet, man.
哥们，你就这么把运动会给毁了 太了不起了
Organized sports are so fascist. It makes me sick.
体育就是法西斯 让我恶心
That's just what I do.
所以我毁了它
Okay. Shit, man. See you around, all right?
靠，回头见哈？
I don't get this school.
我不明白这学校
That was awesome.
你干得很漂亮
Okay, so we stayed up all night making this.
为了做这个，我们一宿没睡
It's awesome. You're really going to like it.
非常棒，你会喜欢的
All yarn work was done by Jenko.
所有故事线索都是延科做的
Okay, Captain, look, the dealers are the popular kids,
队长，是这样 毒贩都是学生名人
but they're not normal popular.
不是一般地受欢迎
They're these crunchy granola dudes that have convinced everyone
他们的生活方式都很健康 让人们相信
that they're cool, and they're not cool.
他们很酷，但真的不酷
It's backwards and unnatural, and it's got to be stopped.
这是倒退，违反自然 必须禁止
Lead dealer, Eric Moison. Alpha dog.
毒贩头是艾里克・默尔森 别名是领头大哥
Sick chicks, killer steeze.
惊艳女郎、轻松时尚 (今年)
Did the AIDS run this year.
组织了艾滋病募捐
He's getting into Berkeley, early admish,
还被伯克利提前录取
and he totally gets me.
而且他完全理解我
Who put this together? Are you autistic?
这都是谁编的？你抑郁症啊？
It is artistic, sir, because the thing is,
是有点艺术，长官，因为
the yarn actually indicates... We're compiling a list
- 这故事暗示… - 我们正在列一个学校里
of suspicious types at school. The users are here.
怀疑对象清单 吸毒者的名单在这
This kid was actually talking to a tree this morning.
这孩子今天早晨冲着一棵树说话
Cut the bullshit!
少说废话！
I want to know who's the supplier.
我想知道供货的是谁
We don't know. That's why there's a question mark on his face.
我们不知道 所以这张脸有个问号
That's not the way his face looks. That's just a question mark.
他的脸并不是这样 这只是个问号
Infiltrate the dealers, find the supplier.
打入毒品贩内部，找出供货商
Simple.
简单
Sounds like you guys really cracked the whole case.
听着好像你们已经成功破案了
Great job. You guys are on fire.
干得棒，激情满怀的
So proud. Like you could do any better?
- 为你们骄傲 - 好像你比我们强？
We just brought down a group of wannabe thugs
我们刚拿下一帮恶棍
stripping down cars in the Garfield High metal shop.
他们在加菲尔德高中 铁匠实习间里拆汽车
What? Meanwhile, you two were standing around
- 什么？ - 这段时间你们俩闲坐一边
finger-popping each other's assholes.
互相"蹼蹼地"抠屁眼
We're not finger-popping each other's assholes.
我们没互相"蹼蹼地"抠屁眼
What we're doing is getting shit done.
我们是完成任务
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
对，其实
I'm about to infiltrate a super high-tech
我正准备潜入一个
drug manufacturing ring in the chemistry classroom.
在化学教室里的超级高科技毒品生产圈
Password! Open the door!
- 口令！ - 开门！
You have to say the password. I'm sorry. What?
- 你得用口令 - 抱歉，什么？
What are you...
你干什…
Geez.
好家伙
What are y'all doing? How'd you get a key in here?
你们在干什么？ 你们哪来的钥匙？
Ms. Griggs gave us one so we could work, tutor, deal Bakugan.
格里格丝先生给了一把 以便我们能干活、辅导、处理爆丸
Bakugan? You dealing drugs?
爆丸？你做毒品生意？
Let me see. You dealing drugs? No.
- 我看看，弄毒品？ - 不
It's just a card game. It's, like, a hybrid card game.
只是个卡片游戏 一种混合卡片游戏
See? They open up. Battle Brawlers.
- 看？打开了 - 爆丸
You're not doing anything illegal? No.
- 没做违法的事？ - 没有
What are you doing in here? I'm here to study.
- 你干什么来了？ - 我来看书
Good. You could use it. You're pretty far behind, so...
好，你能用这个教室 你落后很多，所以
You're behind. I'm ahead.
你才落后，我超前呢
I know everything. Really?
- 我什么都知道 - 真的？
What's a covalent bond?
什么是共价键？
Fuck you, man. I don't need to tell you.
你他妈的，我没必要告诉你
I wasn't trying to be rude. Sorry.
我不是有意冒犯，对不起
I just... I don't think you know everything.
只是，我觉得你不可能什么都知道
I know everything.
我无所不知
Okay.
好吧
What kind of bullshit do they say about a covalent bond in this school?
这所学校里的人 对共价键有什么狗屁说法？
They say it's when two atoms share both their electrons.
他们说共价键 是两个原子共享它们的电子
It helps them to stick together.
这样能帮助它们粘合在一起
I could help you out if you want, tutor you for the test.
如果你愿意，我可以帮你 做考前辅导
What are you doing with all those phones anyway?
你那些电话干什么用的？
I crack and jailbreak kids' phones to try and save for college.
我破解孩子们的电话 为上大学攒点钱
You know, I switch their wireless carriers, get them restricted apps.
我可以换掉无线服务 让他们用受限制的软件
Can you listen in on phone calls and stuff?
你能偷听电话？
No, no, I can't install a spyware to remotely monitor calls
不不，遥控电话我无法装间谍软件
or anything that the mic picks up.
不能偷听麦克拾音
I can't do that at all. Wait, you can't do it?
- 我做不到 - 等等，你做不到？
No, I can't.
做不到
Is he being sarcastic? I don't know.
- 他讽刺人呢吧？ - 不知道
So you can.
这么说你做得到
Liking comic books is popular.
喜欢漫画的人很受欢迎
Environmental awareness, being tolerant.
我有环保意识，很宽容
If I was just born 10 years later, I would have been the coolest person ever.
如果晚出生10年 我会是历史上最酷的人
I know. It's bullshit.
我知道，都是胡扯
You know what?
知道吗
I totally know the cause.
我完全知道起因
Glee. Fuck you, Glee.
他妈的Glee
Man, I got to say, this is kind of awesome.
伙计，我倒是觉得挺不错
I might become popular. I might get in with the popular kids.
我可能会小有名气 也许能混进名人学生堆里
We just have to do something wildly irresponsible to earn their trust.
我们需要做点很不负责任的事 好赢得他们的信任
You saying we should throw a party?
我们来次聚会？
I'll invite Molly, and then Molly will invite Eric,
我会邀请莫莉 然后她就会邀请艾里克
and that'll be the quickest way for me to bro down with him.
要跟艾里克混熟 这个法子最快
Wouldn't it be better if we both infiltrated the cool kids' group?
如果我们俩都混进名人圈 不是更好？
I think it would be better if you get in
我想如果你混进书呆子圈
with the nerdy kids and see what's going on over there.
会更好 看看他们在干什么
That'd be the best thing for the case.
这样对破案最为有利
Yeah. I mean, I guess that makes sense.
嗯，也许有道理
Hello? Hey. Is this Molly?
- 喂？ - 嗨，是莫莉吗？
Speaking.
是我
Hey. It's Schmidt.
我是施密特
It's Doug Schmug McQuaid.
道格施密戈麦奎德
Oh. Hey, man.
嗨，你好
It's so weird that you're calling me.
你给我打电话真是奇了
I pretty much text except for when a random old relative calls.
除了偶尔给年长的亲戚打电话 我一般都用短信
Uh I was just calling 'cause we're costarring in this play together,
我打电话是因为 我们又要做这个戏剧的搭档了
- and... - Hello?
- 而且… - 喂？
Mom, get off the phone!
妈，放下电话！
Oh. Sorry, Doug,
对不起，道格
my teen son. Mom!
- 我的高中生 - 妈！
I love you, honey, Dougie Doug, Douglas McQuaid.
我爱你，宝贝，道基 道格，道格拉斯・麦奎德
Mom, so serious right now! Stop!
妈，我在谈正经事！别说了！
I'm sorry. My mom's such a dick.
对不起，我妈真讨厌
Ugh! She just, like, smothers me with affection and makes me feel like I'm five years old.
她太爱我了 让我觉得自己是5岁的小孩
Wow. You're a sharer. I dig that.
哇，你还谈个人私事，我喜欢
Well, I'm 18 years old, and my mom still packs a lunch for me every day.
我都18岁了 我妈还每天给我准备午饭呢
There was this one month where she bought me 43 stuffed animals.
有一次，她一个月之内给我买了43个绒毛动物玩具
The doctor thought I was gonna spontaneously grow a vagina.
医生都怀疑 我会长出阴道来
I didn't, though, just to be clear.
我声明，我没长哈
Yeah, because you already had one.
因为你早就有
Exactly. I already had one.
没错，早就有
And you don't need two vaginas. You just don't.
你不需要有两个 没必要
Although you could use one as a coin purse.
不过你可以把一个当硬币钱包用
I never got any stuffed animals growing up.
我这些年就没有绒毛动物
Oh, wait, actually, that's not true. I did.
等等，不对，我有过
My dad gave me a stuffed puppy the day he bailed on us.
我爸离开我们那天 送我一只绒毛狗
I'm just fucking with you.
我瞎说呢
That is a weird joke.
这玩笑开的
I thought your dad abandoned your family.
我还以为你爸弃家而逃了呢
No, he did walk out on us, though. Oh.
没有，不过他出走过
But he didn't even leave me a stuffed puppy.
那次连只绒毛狗都没给我
Just broken dreams.
只留下破碎的梦
Oh, man. Well, I guess, to that, I would say,
天，我想，我是说
well, uh,
嗯
that there are some good guys out there,
还是有好人的
and I wouldn't let, you know, one experience
我不会让，你知道，记忆中
taint your memory.
一旦有阴影
Oh, my God.
啊，天啊
Are you getting choked up? I'm sorry if I made you upset.
你硬咽了？ 对不起，我让你难过了
No, it's just, you know, I don't like when guys are mean to girls.
没有，只是 我不喜欢男人欺负女人
Yeah. Well, thanks.
是啊，谢谢你
Normal transition here.
换个话题
Actually, I'm having a party next weekend. You should come!
下周末我这有个聚会 你应该过来
You and Eric and Juario, whatever.
你、艾里克、尤瑞尔，等等
Do you mind if I just put, like, a posting on Facebook?
我把消息放脸谱网上 你不介意吧？
Okay. Yeah, yeah!
好吧，好！
I should call you back.
我回头再打给你
Well, all right, I'll see you at school. You're a great person.
好吧，学校见 你真棒
Bye-bye. Bye, Bye.
- 再见 - 再见
What the fuck are you...
你他妈的干什…
Are y'all throwing a party?
你们要聚会？
What? There's rumors in the Twittersphere.
- 什么？ - 微博上早有风声了
And if any of my officers
如果我的部下
are caught giving alcohol to minors,
给未成年人喝酒 让我抓着
they'll find theyself in prison
咱就监狱见
with a snorkel duct-taped to they mouth
用胶布把潜水通气管缠他嘴上
and me shitting down that snorkel.
我会在管子口上拉屎
That's extremely vivid. Thank you.
形象生动，谢谢
You're the best. You are the best.
你们是最棒的，最棒的
Oh, my God. We love you.
- 天啊 - 我们爱你们
Enjoy the vineyard. You boys be good, now.
- 祝愉快 - 你们乖
Yeah, I can't believe you guys did this for us.
会的，简直不相信 你们俩对我们这么好
Bye!
再见！
"We love you"? What are you doing? Why you saying "I love you" to my mom?
"我们爱你们"？你说啥？ 跟我妈说"我爱你"？
I'm in character. Shut up. It's weird.
- 角色扮演，闭嘴 - 怪
Look, dude, it's kind of like we're brothers.
看呐，哥们，我们真的像兄弟了
Wait, how are we going to buy alcohol?
等等，你怎么买酒？
Dude, I don't have a fake ID.
小子，我可没有假身份
How are we going to get drugs for the party?
怎么弄到毒品？
Oh, no.
天
We got a pound of coke.
一磅可卡因
We're trying to show them a good time, not ruin their fucking lives.
我们只是让他们快活一下 可没想要他们的命
Pound of marijuana?
一磅大麻？
Best party ever. Boo-yah!
- 这聚会真绝了 - 呜啦！
To a brilliant idea
为我们的绝妙主意
from my brilliant brother
为我衷心热爱的
that I love so very much.
非凡的兄弟
And this is going to fucking rock.
这次一定会很棒
Cheers, man. Cheers.
- 干杯 - 干杯
Who invited you guys? I did!
- 谁邀请你们的？ - 我！
The party's here!
来对地方了！
What's up, Zack? Hey, buddy.
- 还好吧，扎克？ - 嗨，哥们
What's up, Roman?
你好吗，罗曼？
This is crazy. This is, like, the craziest thing I've ever been a part of.
这太疯狂了 这是我参加过的最疯狂的聚会
Where is Eric, man? He said he'd be here.
艾里克呢？他说会来的
Do we have enough chips?
土豆片还够吗？
Is this playlist too dance-y?
这串音乐是不是太像舞曲了？
Feels too dance-y. Too dance-y?
- 感觉是 - 舞曲？
What are you talking about? I don't know, it just feels dance-y.
- 你说什么呢？ - 不知道，觉得节奏太强
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
你们在干什么？
That's my mom's Kokopelli vase. I got it, I got it.
- 那是我妈的高高飘丽花瓶 - 给我，给我
Doug, Doug, hey!
道格，道格，嗨！
Hey, Paul Blart: Molly Cop.
嗨，莫莉小影星
Such a bad joke.
这玩笑太臭了
Terrible, terrible.
臭，臭
You guys know each other, right? Yeah.
- 都认识吧？ - 认识
Get ready, get ready, there's Eric. Wait for the signal.
准备好，准备好，艾里克来了 等候暗号
And then you come in here looking like a rock-solid 10.
你这一出场 就像十足的大明星
What?
什么？
What's up, man, how you doing?
嗨，哥们，还好吧？
Eco Suave.
酷毙了
Whoa.
哇
Wow, so I'm really digging this decor.
哇，我好喜欢这布置
Very Native American.
特有土著印第安的味道
Yeah, our parents are actually
是啊，我父母
really into Native American... Let's rock and roll.
- 特喜欢土著印… - 来舞舞吧
- Sorry. - What are y'all doing?
- 抱歉 - 你们都在干什么？
Come on. Did you guys even see Eric?
- 得了 - 你们看见艾里克了吗？
Seriously, did you not see Eric?
你真的没看见？
No offense, man, but your brother sucks.
无意冒犯哈，你弟太差劲
Yo, this is butt. There's, like, no hot dudes here.
这聚会太没劲 一个名人都没有
Man, let's bounce. We're out of here, man.
- 咱们撤吧 - 我们走了哈
No, no, no, come on, you guys just got here, you just got here.
别别，你们才刚到 没多久
Come on, let me at least give you a tour.
别走，至少让我带你们转转
Okay, boys, come on, we did it, we can do this, just go,
大家快点，我们以前干过 没问题，快弄
just go as fast as you possibly can.
越快越好
Taking out the SIM card. Taking out the SIM card.
把SIM卡取出
กำ Taking down Eric with the SIM card information กำ
用SIM卡上的信息 拿下艾里克
Come on, CSI the shit out of this thing.
快，拿出犯罪证据
Are you drunk? No.
- 喝多了？ - 没
Have you even been drunk before?
以前喝醉过吗？
No, but?Give me this.
- 没有，但… - 给我
What? Can we get some bitches up in here?
- 干嘛？ - 来几个妹子，行吗？
'Cause it's just boys right now.
现在都是秃小子
No, you can't get any bitches up here.
不行，不能招妹子来
This is my parents' bedroom.
这是我父母的房间
What the fuck, bro? Some privacy! Shit, shit, shit!
- 靠，哥们，给点隐私！ - 他妈的！他妈的！
And that is a really gross three-way.
这个一对二，可不咋地
But what was the girl in the back doing?
后面那女孩在干什么？
Warehouse rave in Ellsworth.
大型少年聚会
Cool, yeah.
酷吧
Hey, man, thank you for the hospitality,
嗨，哥们，谢谢你的热情款待
but we got to get going. You know how it is, yeah?
但我们真的得走了 你知道的，对吧？
Dude, tell me about it.
我还蒙在鼓里呢
Is it ready? He's gonna leave right now.
好了吗？他马上撤了
It's extracting right now.
正在提取
Dude, it's now or never! Is it ready or not?
呆子，勿失良机，好没好啊？
Read this. "Please wait. Extracting data from SIM card."
你看 "请稍候，正在提取信息"
Shit! It's a bust.
靠！吹了
- Keep it casual. - Yeah.
- 随便点 - 好
Go with the flow, dude. Cool, man.
- 顺其自然 - 酷
I don't like to make plans or whatever. You got it.
- 我不喜欢计划 - 没错
Thank you again, though, man. All right.
- 谢谢你 - 行了
Eric, Eric, Eric. Hey, man, what's up?
艾里克，艾里克，嗨，还好吗？
Hey, why you here, Scott?
斯格特，你来这干什么？
What, Kennedy High isn't having any parties tonight?
肯尼迪中学今晚没有聚会？
No, I heard you guys were partying with some new stuff.
没有，我听说你们跟新来的聚会
Wanted to know your hookup so me and my boys can get in on it.
想认识一下你的朋友 我和我的兄弟们也好掺合
Got other commitments on that front, so, you know...
在这方面我另有承诺 所以，你知道…
I wasn't asking.
我没求你
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
咳，咳，咳，行了
Take five, take five, man, let me get this. I got this.
歇会，歇会，让我来，我能处理好
Yeah? You sure? I got this one.
- 是吗？有把握？ - 没问题
Hey, big player, I don't know who you are.
嗨，大腕，我还不知道你是谁呢
Don't worry about who I am. I'm worried about it.
- 我是谁无所谓 - 我担心啊
Why? 'Cause you're at my party right now, dude.
- 为什么？ - 因为你来我这聚会
This is my temple, this is where I come to find peace, dawg,
这是我的神庙 我在这找到平静，猪
and you're coming in here like an emotional bull in a china shop,
你上这来 就像瓷器店里情绪激动的蛮牛
metaphorically knocking over vases, messing with my crew,
就好象到处碰碎花瓶 把我的朋友圈搅得一团糟
and I'm like, "What, Scott, what, Scott, what, what, what, what, Scott?"
我就得说："什么啊，斯格特 什么啊，斯格特？"
It's that kind of party? Yeah, dude.
- 这是聚会？ - 是啊
Matter of fact, it's getting hot in here, huh?
说实在的，还真是有点热呢
No, it's getting real. It's getting very real.
- 别，还较真了 - 真较真了
Yeah. It's like seven strangers living in one house. True story.
对，就像真实故事中 七个陌生人同住一个屋檐下
You want Real World? Yeah, let's do it, man.
- 你要Real World？ - 没错，来吧
Come on. What's your Real... Here's Real World.
- 来吧，你的Real - 这呢
What was that? Did you hear that?
怎么了？听见了吗？
Real enough for you?
够真实的吧？
Schmidt. Doug.
施密特，道格
What do I do? Hit him!
- 我该怎么办？ - 揍他！
Shit! That hurt worse than when he hit me!
妈的！比他揍我还疼！
Fight normal.
正规点
Yo, I'm serious.
你，我说真的
Sorry.
对不起
I'll fucking kill you! I'm sorry! I'm very sorry!
- 我他妈宰了你！ - 对不起！真对不起！
Seriously, use your words, use your words!
真的，动口别动手，动口别动手！
I kicked him in the nuts.
我踢了他蛋蛋
Fight's over, dude! Fight's over! Fight's over!
不打了，混蛋！不打了！不打了！
No, watch my mom's shit, man!
呀，小心我妈的东西
I'm gonna fucking kill you! You'll knock over my mom's vase!
- 我他妈宰了你 - 你把我妈的花瓶砸碎了！
Fuck your mom's vase! Fuck this!
- 去你妈的花瓶 - 去他妈的！
Oh, shit!
该死！
Yeah!
好啊！
That's my brother!
瞧我哥！
That was insane! You're so cool!
- 简直太疯了！ - 你真酷毙了！
Did you see that shit? That was crazy.
你们看见了吗？太疯狂了
Oh, shit,
哦，该死
when did I get stabbed?
我什么时候被刺的？
That's awesome.
太了不起了
Yeah!
好！
Is that a cop?
那是警察吗？
Where?
在哪儿？
No, it's not. Here.
不，不是，给你
Oh, I'm so glad we're going back to get my phone.
我真高兴我们回去拿手机
I just hope we don't wake up Schmidty.
就怕吵醒施密特
Oh, my God, he's a policeman now.
天，他都是警察了
It's like we're living with a narc.
好像我们跟缉毒特警住一起似的
The boy is an angel.
这孩子是天使
Pull it out!
拔出来！
Pull it out! Pull it out! Pull it out!
拔出来！拔出来！拔出来！
Sorry!
对不起啦！
Okay, let's take some shots.
好，喝几口厉害的
Shots, shots!
喝几口！
That's like us fucking Mother Earth without a condom.
那就像不带套 跟大地做爱
What the fuck is going on?
他妈的怎么回事？
Annie, hang on.
安妮，等等
Are you fucking kidding me?
你们他妈的耍我吗？
Get out of my house. I said get out! The party's over!
滚出去，我说了滚！ 聚会结束了！
I'm sorry, Mom, I'm sorry!
对不起，妈，对不起！
The mom is coming!
妈妈来了！
Listen to me! Chill out! Chill out!
- 听我说！ - 冷静！冷静！
Let go of me! SCHMIDT: You're embarrassing me
- 放开我！ - 朋友面前
in front of my friends! Get back here, you shit!
- 你让我好难堪 - 回来，混蛋！
Dude, that was so crazy, man.
哥们，太疯狂了
I swear, best party I've been to in years.
我发誓，多年来这是最棒的聚会
Dude, I'm doing crazy stuff like that,
哥们，我就是这么疯的
like, all the time, man. I bet you are.
- 一直都这样 - 绝对的
Dude, I'm so amped right now, God!
哥们，我太兴奋了，天啊！
You, dude, I like you, man.
哥们，我喜欢你
How do you feel about making a little extra money?
想挣点外快吗？
Whatever it is, I'm in.
不管是啥，算我一个
All right, here's the deal.
好，这样
Okay, I can't sell all this shit on my own, but I only bring in people I like.
我一个人卖不完那么多 但我只拉我喜欢的人进来
Okay, you do good, maybe we bring you in on what we're doing,
你做得好 或许我也把你拉进来
I introduce you to my hookup. How's that sound?
我介绍你加入我的圈子 怎么样？
Cool with me. My man.
- 我没问题 - 老弟
That is my man...
这才是我的老弟
That was nuts. I lost you guys.
真见鬼，找不到你们了
Um... Hey, thank you again for the party, man.
嗨，再次谢谢你的聚会，哥们
Yo, yo.
唷，唷
Come on!
开始了！
I love dick"?
"我爱"？
You think that's funny?
你觉得好玩吗？
"Wonder Years douche"?
"Wonder Years傻蛋"？
What kind of a sick animal draws
给一个8岁的孩子嘴上
an ejaculating penis into an 8-year-old's mouth?
画个射精的阳物 这是什么样的病态动物啊？
It's arguably, like, an airplane throwing up.
也可能是飞机吐白线
You think I don't know that's a dick and balls?
你以为我不认识阳物和蛋蛋啊？
I know all about dick and balls!
我清楚得很！
I partied with Robert Downey Jr. before he got sober,
我参加过小罗伯特唐尼的晚会 后来他才清醒
when he was really fucked up and a lot of fun!
那时他喝得一塌糊涂 还胡来！
You know what? From now on, you're gonna do some chores.
知道吗？ 从现在起，你们得做家务
You're gonna wash the laundry, you're gonna fold it,
要洗衣服、叠衣服
you're gonna do the dishes, you're gonna mow the lawn...
要刷碗、剪草坪
Dude, I have a surprise for you.
哥们，我给你个惊喜
Last night at the party, I took Eric's phone
聚会时，我拿了艾里克的手机
and I had Zack put this monitoring device in it,
我让扎克放了一个监视器
so we're gonna get to hear every single thing that little prick is up to.
那杂种的什么事 我们都能听清楚了
Dude, I don't know if that was a good idea.
哥们，我不知道这主意好不好
What?
什么？
What if you had gotten found out? But it worked.
- 你被发现了怎么办？ - 但有效
This is, like, the smartest move I've ever pulled,
这是我们最聪明的一步棋
so, I'm sorry, what are you getting mad at me for?
对不起 你为什么这么生我的气？
I'm not getting mad at you. I'm glad you have something to do.
我没生你的气 你有些事做，我高兴
Good.
很好
What's up?
怎么样啊？
Great job, Schmidt.
干得好，施密特
Password! Kneel before Zod!
- 口令！ - 跪拜萨德！
You may enter.
你可以进来了
Thank you, Zod.
谢谢萨德
Let's tap that wire, huh?
我们来窃听一下？
We were just about to go outside with a bunch of chemicals.
我们正要带化学药品出去
We were going to test what blows up.
试验一下那种能爆炸
There's no reason the wiretap is super urgent, right?
你窃听的事没那么紧急吧？
Not that I can think of that would make sense.
想不出紧急的理由
Go for it, go for it.
加点，加点
Look out. Go, go, go!
- 小心 - 快跑！快！
Yes!
对了！
Yes, that's what I'm talking about!
对了，这就是我说的！
That's what I'm talking about!
这就是我说的！
I love this science shit!
我喜欢他娘的理科！
This is what you guys do all day? Let's do it again.
你们整天就干这个？ 再来一次
Are you texting Molly?
给莫莉发短信？
Uh, what?
什么？
I don't... Molly, uh...
我没…莫莉…
Maybe. Is that...
也许，怎…
Whoa, it's cool, man, come on.
哇，酷，哥们，别不好意思
I'm not some, like, '50s letterman who pins a girl.
我不是那种50年代运动员，盯住女孩不放
I mean, yeah, we blow each other sometimes, but it's not a thing.
我是说，虽然有时互相吹箫 但那也没什么
I just, like... I don't know, I don't believe in possessions, ja feel?
只是，怎么说呢 我不相信占有，你觉得呢？
Ja feel, ja definitely feel.
你觉得，你绝对觉得
Yeah. Schmidty?
- 绝对 - 施密特？
Schmidty.
施密特
Phyllis.
菲利斯
I'll be right back, dude. Okay.
- 我马上回来 - 好吧
Hey. How are you?
嗨，你好啊！
How is my favorite police officer? Okay.
- 我的警察宝贝怎么样啊？ - 好了
Your mother told me that you are undercover.
你妈妈告诉我你卧底呢
Listen, now is not a really good time.
听着，现在不是时候
Are you undercover right now?
你现在正在卧底？
Yes, it means I'm undercover right now.
是，现在正在卧底
Are those the bad guys over there?
那边的都是坏蛋？
Do they have guns? Oh, my God. Oh, God, this is so exciting.
他们有枪吗？天啊 天啊，太刺激了
I have got to call Annie. She is gonna die.
我得打电话给安妮，她会昏过去
I heard that that Jenko boy is your partner.
我听说延科那孩子是你搭档
Where is my phone? Okay, okay.
- 我的手机呢？ - 好了好了
Shut your fucking mouth.
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut your fucking mouth, you understand me? Shh...
闭上你的臭嘴 明白吗？
Let's go check this out.
我去看看怎么回事
I will straight-up punch you in the face if you do not shut up.
你再不闭嘴 我就一拳打到你脸上
There is no... A straight-up face punch.
- 没有… - 直打到脸上
I swear to God, you're gonna get me killed.
我发誓，你会让我丧命的
Hey, yo. That is...
- 嗨，唷 - 那…
Shit! She just tried to grab my dick, dude!
妈的，她上来要抓我小弟弟
What? You tried to grab his... She tried to grab my junk.
- 什么？你想抓他的… - 她要抓我的家伙
She was like, "Oh, my God, I have arthritis,"
她说："天，我有关节炎
"it hurts my hand, I need to grab a handful of that dick."
"手很疼，得抓住那鸡鸡"
I was like, "Get the fuck off me!"
我说："你妈一边去！"
She said, "I need to grab a handful of that dick"?
她说"得抓住鸡鸡"？
And it felt good, but then it felt weird for a second,
感觉还不错 可马上就不对劲了
so I pushed her. We got to get out of here.
所以我推了她一把，我们得赶快离开这
All right, cool, let's get the...
酷，咱们…
Ah, so your parents are just cool with having people over whenever?
那么是说你父母很酷 常常允许你带人到家里去？
Yeah, you know, they're out most nights.
是，他们晚上大多不在家
Pretty laissez-faire about the whole thing.
属于完全不干涉那种
You're so lucky your parents don't give a shit about you.
父母不管你，你太幸运了
Right?
是吧？
This place is awesome. Yeah.
- 这地方真棒 - 是啊
Hey.
嗨
Hey, what's up?
嗨，咋样？
How's it going?
还好吗？
Wow, that's a bigger hug than I was expecting.
这拥抱比我期望的带劲多了
Sorry. I'm happy to see you.
抱歉，见到你我真高兴
Yeah. Yeah, me, too.
是啊，我也是
Hey. Oh, hey.
- 嗨 - 嗨
Good? Mmm-hmm.
好啊
All right, come on. Yeah, let's...
- 走吧 - 走，我…
I brought tacos, so that's cool.
我带了玉米片，好吧
กำ Try to turn it, try to turn it, spoiler alert
转过来，转过来，别太过火
กำ Spoiler alert, spoiler alert! กำ
别太过火，别太过火
Hey, boys, this eco-pussy is going down today.
嗨，几位，这个环保家伙 今天走下坡路了
กำ Take down eco-pussy
拿下环保佬
กำ Mother Earth, Mother Earth is dying
大地，大地命在旦夕
กำ And when it rains
下雨的时候
กำ It means that beautiful bitch is crying กำ
那是贱人在哭泣
It's really not a planet. It's for sure a planet.
- 真不是行星 - 肯定是行星
Pluto is a planet.
冥王星是行星
It's ready! It used to be a planet.
- 好了！ - 以前是行星
It's ready. Not any more.
- 好了 - 不再是了
กำ Reduce, reuse
减量，再利用
กำ Recycle กำ
回收
I'm embarrassed.
我不好意思了
I always feel exposed after playing. Do not feel exposed.
- 弹完总感觉我暴露了 - 别这么感觉
I got to use the bathroom.
我得用厕所
Is it in there? ERIC: Yeah, yeah, right up there, dude.
- 是在那吗？ - 对对，上面，哥们
All right, all right, all right, all right. God damn that.
好了，好了 该死的
The mic is live and we can hear how the other half lives.
麦克风开着 我们能听见他们那边
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
I heard something.
我听到什么
Hey, can I ask you something? Sit down.
嗨，我能问你点事吗？坐下
Okay.
好
I just want to make sure that you and Eric are going to be careful
我只想提醒 你和艾里克都务必要小心
with whatever it is that you're getting involved in.
不管我们参与的事情是什么
Yeah, I promise we will.
好，我保证
It would just suck if something bad happened,
如果有什么不测 就太恶心了
because you're a good guy.
因为，你是个好男人
Yeah, no, I feel the same way about you,
是啊，我觉得你也是
except girl version.
当然是好女人
You're a girl.
你是女的
I am. Yeah.
- 我是 - 是啊
That's why I put this dress on,
所以我才穿了裙子
to remind you. Exactly.
- 好提醒你 - 就是
Are you excited about the play? Yes.
- 演戏的事，你是不是很兴奋？ - 是
Yeah, you were just
是啊，你站那
right in there with excitement. Yes.
- 就兴奋 - 没错
No hesitash. I'm very excited.
- 毫不犹豫 - 我特兴奋
Yeah.
是
Does that make me a super nerd?
我那样是不是特傻？
No, not at all.
一点也不
We get to act together.
我们演戏是绝配
What a vagina. He has no chance with her.
真是娘们，他跟她根本没戏
So...
那么…
Shit. Sorry.
- 妈的 - 对不起
You're on the prom committee. Mmm-hmm.
你在毕业舞会委员会里
Do you think it's going to be fun?
你觉得舞会会很好玩吗？
Did she just bring up prom on her own?
她主动提舞会的事？
She did, she just brought up prom. What is she doing?
- 是，她自己提的 - 她在干嘛？
I think it's going to be awesome.
我想会很棒
Prom eats a dong. Multiple dongs.
- 舞会没劲 - 太没劲
All right, anyone who says
好了，那些
they don't care about prom actually secretly does.
说舞会没劲的 其实暗地里最感兴趣
Who we gonna take to the prom? No one's going to prom with us.
我们带谁去啊？ 没人跟我们跳舞
Come on, picture it. You pull up in a white stallion of a limo.
想象一下 你们乘坐白色豪华礼宾车来到舞场
You got fine-ass honeys with you.
胳膊挎着漂亮美眉
You're dressed to the nines with your best buds.
穿着笔挺的礼服 还有女郎陪伴
Doves fly out behind you, slow motion.
鸽子在你身后飞翔，慢动作
Doves. Why doves?
鸽子，为什么是鸽子？
'Cause doves make you look like a badass, that's why.
因为鸽子让你看上去 像个坏蛋，这就是为什么
I am pretty skeptical,
我说不准
but maybe, if someone fun asked me, I would go.
但，如果邀请我的是个有趣的人 也许我会去
Aren't... Isn't... Aren't you and Eric...
你…不是…你和艾里克不是…
Wouldn't you and Eric go together?
你不跟艾里克一起去？
Not that I know of.
我怎么不知道
Would you...
你会…
He's going to choke.
该呛着了
He always chokes. He's going to choke, wait for it.
他总呛着 他会的，等着瞧
So would...
那，你…
Would you...
你会…
Mayb...
也许…
Oh, my God. Are you okay? Yeah.
- 天啊，你没事吧？ - 没事
That is the actual sound of choking.
那是真正呛着的声音
I was wondering if you...
我在想，你会不会…
Would you
你会不会
maybe want to go
也许，你会不会
with me to prom?
跟我去？
Would you want to go to me... Maybe with me to prom?
你想跟我去… 跟我去毕业舞会吗？
Yes.
木目
I would love to go to prom with you.
我愿意跟你去舞会
What? She just said yes!
什么？她居然答应了！
Whoa. Wow.
哇哇
Good for you, Doug.
不错啊，道格
Thank you for asking.
谢谢你的邀请
Put her there, man.
握手为证
Just put... Put it right there.
就握手吧
I'm putting it right there.
我把它放在这了
Yeah. There you guys are.
啊，你们在这啊
What's up, my man?
怎么样啊，我的兄弟？
Hi. How you doing?
- 嗨 - 你好吗？
Whazzup? Yeah.
- 有新闻？ - 嗯
Doug... Okay, settle an argument.
道格…来解决我们的纷争
You and your brother aren't related, right?
你和你哥没血缘关系，对不？
'Cause you look totally different.
因为你们长得不像
He's adopted.
他是被收养的
We all suspect from a very lame family.
我们都怀疑是否出于什么破家庭
Where is he tonight?
这会他在哪？
Probably at home with those lame tools he hangs outwith. I don't know.
也许在家，鼓弄破工具 跟工具瞎混，我不知道
You know how Tom Cruise is always pissed off at Rain Man?
知道为什么汤姆・克鲁斯 对《雨人》那么嗤之以鼻吗？
That's like my life, except Brad is really shitty at math.
那就像我的生活 还不算布莱德的数学糟糕透顶
Your brother's kind of a dick.
你弟弟真操蛋
Well, yeah
是啊
he kind of is, isn't he?
有点儿，是吧？
Don't listen to that.
别听了
I don't give a fuck.
我才不在乎呢
Dude, Eric is the funniest IM-er.
哥们，艾里克是发短信的人中最好玩的
Oh, fuck.
他妈的
Oh, hey, guys. It's so funny seeing you here.
嗨，两位，在这看见你们真可笑
How are you? Guess what, I don't care.
你们好，猜怎么着 我是无所谓
We just closed our third high school operation.
我们刚刚结了第三个高中案
And check what we found at Kennedy.
看我们在肯尼迪高中找到了什么
Looks like we're going to have to do your job for you.
看起来 好像你们的活得我们替你们干
Your drugs is spreading to different schools now, sucker.
你们的毒品已经扩散到其他学校了，笨蛋
You failed to stop the outbreak, and you have no leads!
你们不但没阻止扩散 而且也没找到头头
We are running out of time!
我们时间紧迫
You either find the supplier,
找不到供货商
or I'm gonna jump your asses off Jump Street!
我就把你们的屁股踢出跳跳街！
I totally understand where you're coming from, sir,
我完全明白你的意思，长官
but, look, I heard Eric talking on the phone yesterday
但是，昨天我听见艾里克 在电话里
with somebody that sounded very suspect
跟什么人说话，我很怀疑
with a stuffed piata. about meeting up
他要和彩饰陶罐碰面
Is that a code for sex?
那是性的代号吗？
Piata? Really? Yep.
- 彩饰陶罐？真的？ - 真的
Remember that wiretap I put on Eric's phone?
记得艾里克手机里的监听器吗？
While you were having the time of your life last night, I was listening.
昨晚你风花雪月的时候 我在监听
I overheard a phone call between Eric and some dude about a piata.
听到艾里克和另一个人说起彩饰陶罐
That's all you heard?
这就些？
Yep.
对
I am so nervous.
我太紧张了
We are about to premiere in front of the whole school.
我们将要在全校师生面前 首次亮相
I apologize in advance if I throw up on you onstage.
如果我在台上时吐到你身上 我提前说对不起哈
Serious question, though.
严肃的问题
How do I look?
我的装束如何
Ravishing.
夺魂摄魄
Is it too sexy of an outfit?
这套服装太性感了？
Bend the knee a little bit.
弯下膝盖
Yep, it is.
是啊
Oh, it's going to be so much easier having you onstage with me.
台上有你陪着 我轻松多了
I am so happy that I met you.
遇到你我真高兴
You're, like, the only guy that I can really trust.
你是唯一我能信任的人
Yep. That's me.
是，是我
Doug.
道格
Potassium nitrate.
硝酸钾
Don't hate. It's great.
不要恨它，它很伟大
It can act as an oxidizer.
它可充当氧化剂
I didn't know that, but now I'm wiser.
至今我才得明悉
It has a crystalline structure.
晶体结构组成它
If you can't respect that, you're a butt muncher.
忽视这点是傻瓜
It's a key ingredient in gunpowder.
制作炸药离不了
K-NO-three, don't give no grief.
硝酸钾，伤心吧
It can be used to make corned beef.
牛肉罐头也用它
It's also known as saltpeter.
它的别名是硝石
Brad? Shit.
- 布莱德？ - 该死
Where are you going?
你去哪？
I don't want to look like it's like I'm wearing makeup.
我不想让人们看出来我化了妆
Right. Doug! HL
- 对 - 道格！嗨
Brad!
布莱德
Whoa. What are you wearing?
哇，你穿的什么？
Potassium nitrate. Thanks for noticing.
硝酸钾，谢谢你注意到了
I need to borrow you.
我要借你一用
Now's not a good time, Brad.
时候不对，布莱德
Mmm-hmm. It's a really good time.
时候正对
'Cause my piata is killing me.
因为彩饰陶罐要杀了我
Is that code for a sex thing?
是性事的代号吗？
It's leaving the parking lot.
它就要离开停车场
Mmm-hmm. Piata?
彩饰陶罐？
Molly, uh,
莫莉
I will be right back. I need to help Brad with something, okay?
我马上回来 我得帮他做点事，好吗？
I just need to help Brad with something real quick.
帮布莱德会很快的
What? No. What? I promise you...
- 什么？不！ - 我保证…
Do you understand how soon the show is starting?
你不明白演出马上就要开始吗？
I swear to you I will be back in time for curtain.
我对你发誓 启幕前就回来
I swear. I swear to you. Tell me you understand how soon...
- 我发誓，发誓 - 告诉我你明白…
What? Are you kidding me?
啊？你这不是耍我吗？
What did I say? What did I say?
我说什么来着？
See? Whose wiretap is working for him now, huh?
看看，谁的监听管用？
Shit.
该死
Fuck!
靠！
You told me not to worry about the tickets!
你跟我说过不用担心吃罚单
I thought they made us look cool.
我想这会让我们看着酷
Cones, cones... Driver's ed car.
- 路锥，路锥… - 教练车
I'm driving. No, you're not.
- 我来开 - 不不
I never get to drive. I'm driving this time. Fine! Drive!
- 我没开过，这次我开 - 好！你开！
Hey, guys. Just borrowing this for one sec.
- 嗨，小伙子们 - 就借- 会
Sure. Go. Go, go, go, go.
- 好吧 - 快快快
Guys, hey, wait. Guys, you're not on the list.
嗨，等等，你们不在名单上
Hey, guys, wait! Ah, who cares?
嗨，等等！算了
Holy fucking shit. No fucking way.
- 真他妈的 - 不可能
Those are the guys from the park.
这些人就是公园那帮
That's just too crazy.
太不可思议了
What do you think's in that thing?
你觉得那里面是啥？
I don't know, money, drugs.
不知道，钱，毒品
They could be a new buyer, or they could be the supplier.
他们可能是新主顾 或者是供货商
If it's good, you'll hear from me.
如果好使，我会告诉你消息的
If it's not good, you'll hear from me about telling you how it's not good.
如果不好，我也会告诉你为什么
Makes sense.
可以理解
Get the fuck out of here. Yeah, no worries, man.
你他妈快离开这里 好，别担心
I'll see you guys.
再见
We definitely got to follow them and find out, though.
我们得跟踪他们好查明事实
Get down! Get down! Get down! Get down!
- 低头 低头 - 低头 低头
What are you doing? If they see us,
- 干嘛？ - 如果被看见了
just pretend like you're sucking my dick.
就假装你在给我吹箫
What? No! Yes. Stop.
- 什么？不！ - 别吵了
You pretend like you're sucking my dick.
你假装吹我的
No, just pretend like you're sucking my dick.
不，快，假装给我吹箫
Why am I automatically blowing you?
为什么我自动吹你？
'Cause you're in a fucking Peter Pan costume!
因为你他妈的穿着《彼得潘》的服装！
Okay.
好吧
Okay, let's go. Let's go, let's go.
好了，快走，快
Go, go, go. Okay, fine, we'll follow them.
- 快快快 - 好了，跟踪他们
But we need to be back in 30 minutes for curtain.
但30分钟之内 必须在启幕前赶回去
Dude, did you just hit the teacher brake?
你踩了教练脚刹？
Yeah, you're following too close, dude.
对，你太近了
They're going to make us. Well, if I go too far back,
- 他们会发现的 - 要是太远了
it's going to look even more suspicious, so just stop.
就更容易受怀疑，别踩了
God, just let me do my thing.
天，让我做我的事
I know what I'm doing.
我知道自己在干什么
Seriously, if you do that again, I'm going to Whac-A-Mole you in the balls.
我严肃警告，你再踩闸 我就揍扁你的蛋蛋
Just stay back.
离远点
I could not be more serious. Take your foot off the brake.
- 我再严肃不过了 - 把脚从闸上挪开
No. I'm not... No. Take your foot off the brake!
- 不，不挪 - 把脚挪开！
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
哦，该死！该死！
Look what you did! Look what you did!
- 看你干的好事！ - 看你干的好事！
What the fuck? You non-driving motherfuckers!
你他妈的会开车吗？混蛋！
Get the fuck out of the car!
给我出来！
Oh, fuck. Lock the door! Lock the door!
- 哦，靠 - 锁上门！锁上门！
What do I do? Go away!
我怎么办？走开！
What are you, a fucking Keebler Elf?
你是"奇宝精灵"？
Get him out of that car!
给我出来！
No, no! It's fucking ZZ Top!
- 不不！ - 是他妈的ZZ托普乐队！
No, no! No, no, no! It's fucking ZZ Top!
- 不不不！ - 是ZZ托普！
Like an angry walrus!
像暴怒的海象！
I stomp the car now! Oh, my God!
- 我把车跺扁！ - 哦，天啊！
Stomp! Stomp! Oh, shit.
- 跺！跺！ - 啊，该死
Okay. Okay. Oh, my God! Stop, dude! Go!
- 好，好 - 天啊！行了，哥们！ 开车！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
天啊！天啊！
Just let me drive! Stop hitting me!
- 让我开！ - 别打我！
Dude, watch out!
哥们，小心！
Will you stop front-seat driving? Get your hands off the wheel!
别指手画脚 把手拿开！
Man, you just hit two people back there!
嗨，你刚撞了两个人
You stop. I'm not... Take your hands off. Shit!
- 你停手，我不… - 把手拿开，该死！
We're stuck in traffic! Oh, shit.
- 我们卡在这 - 哦，该死！
Shit, they're coming! They're coming! What?
- 妈的，他们过来了， - 什么？ 过来了！
Oh, my God, dude.
哦，天
What do we do?
我们怎么办？
What the... What the...
见鬼…见鬼…
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
娘的，娘的
Oh, shit.
哦，他娘的
Oh, shit. What's wrong with you? Run!
- 哦，娘的 - 怎么了？跑啊！
I can't! I'm wearing tights!
跑不动，穿着紧身袜呢！
I got skinny jeans on! It's the same fucking thing!
我穿的是紧身牛仔裤 一样的！
They're going to make us, or kill us.
他们会追到我们，杀了我们的
Porsche! Porsche! Police! Get out of the car, douche!
- 保时捷！ - 警察！下车，阔佬！
I'm on a call here, jackass.
我在听电话，混帐
That's right. Go to sleep, bitch. You just got head-butted, motherfucker!
对了，睡觉去吧 你头撞地了，混蛋！
Go, go, go, go, go, go! Shit.
- 快快快！ - 娘的
Check around for a gun or something, all right?
找找有没有枪之类的
Where? Where? There's no glove compartment
哪？哪？没储物箱
in this shitty-ass car! There's golf balls and this.
这破车！有高尔夫球和这个
What am I supposed to do with this? I don't know, man!
- 这个怎么用？ - 不知道！
I've never been in a freeway chase before!
从来没在高速上追过车
Watch out! It's going to explode! It's going to go!
小心，要爆炸了！ 会爆炸！
What happened? I don't know.
- 怎么了？ - 不知道
It just didn't explode. That's weird.
- 没爆炸 - 奇怪
Can anybody tell me where my Peter is?
谁知道我的彼得在哪里？
French! You're not my first choice, but I need you to go on as Peter.
法兰奇！你不是我的第一选择 但我需要你替补彼得的角色
Oh, gosh. And I've been in character for months now.
哦，天，几个月来我一直活在角色中
Great. Nobody cares.
太棒了，没人在意的
Come on! Another traffic jam?
快！又堵车了？
I'm sorry I didn't check the traffic report
对不起，追车开始前
before we got in a car chase! Let's go! Come on!
- 没听交通报道 - 快跑！快！
Come on. Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- 快，快跑，快跑！ - 妈的！
Shit!
莫莉 你到底在哪？？ ？
Are you texting? No, I'm not texting!
- 你在写短信？ - 没，没写！
Yes, you are! You're texting! No, I'm not!
- 写了！你在按键呢！ - 没有！
Okay, almost done.
好，马上就好
"LOL."
"大笑"
I'm driving!
我开！
Why do you always jump over the car like that?
你为什么总是那样跃过汽车？
Hi. Hi. How are you?
嗨，你好！
Hi. God damn, you are beautiful.
- 嗨 - 你他娘的真美
Oh. Hi. You are fine as shit.
- 哦，嗨 - 你好得像大粪
Don't worry. Someone will pick you up.
别担心，会有人接你的
Wow. Hurry. Just drive.
- 哇 - 快，开你的车
Wait. Pick me up?
等等，接我？
They're coming! They're coming! I got an idea.
- 他们来了，来了！ - 我有主意
Why don't you text them and ask them to stop chasing us?
为什么不发短信给他们 告诉他们别追了？
Oh, shit!
哦，该死的！
He's got a gun!
他有枪！
I'm going to throw this thing at him!
我用这个扔他！
Okay, you don't have to narrate everything!
好，不用通报！
Just throw it! Okay! Okay, okay!
- 扔啊！ - 好好！
It's going to explode! Oh, my God! Roll up the windows!
- 会爆炸的！ - 天，摇起车窗！
What the fuck is that going to do? Roll it up!
- 爆炸会怎样？ - 摇起来！
I don't fucking care! Just do it! Oh, God!
- 我他妈不管！做就是了！ - 天
I really thought that one was going to explode.
我真的以为会爆炸的
Oh, shit!
哦，该死！
Look in the glove compartment for a gun.
储物箱里有枪吗？
What are you talking about? We're in a pink Bug!
你说什么呢？ 在粉甲壳虫里？
I don't care. Look in the goddamn glove compartment!
不管，看看该死的储物箱
What the hell?
怎么会？
Shoot Oh, my God. Okay! Okay!
- 开枪 - 天，好！好！
Shoot the gun! Shoot the gun!
开枪啊！开枪！
Can't get a good shot, man! I can't get a good shot!
打不准啊！ 没法瞄准！
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit. Take the shot!
- 奶奶的，奶奶的 - 开枪！
Take the shot! Just shoot him! Let's go!
开枪！打他！开啊！
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
奶奶的，奶奶的
Shoot! Shoot! Shit, shit...
- 开枪！ - 奶奶的…
That's what exploded? Holy shit. That was crazy.
爆炸了？天啊 疯狂啊
Why did you shoot for me?
为什么替我开枪？
You weren't shooting, you were choking,
你不开，就在那咽着
so I had to save us. I was going to shoot.
- 我得救我们俩 - 我要开的
You always do this, every single time. What?
- 你总是这样，每次都是 - 什么？
Seriously, just take me back to school, man.
说真的，把我送回学校
If I miss this play, Molly's going to freak out and she's not going to go to prom with me.
我误了场，莫莉会崩溃的 她就不会当我的舞伴了
Are you fucking serious right now? Fuck, yes, I'm serious!
- 你现在认真了？ - 妈的，对，认真了
Can't believe you made me late. You're so selfish.
简直不能相信你让我迟到 真自私
I'm selfish? Yes, you're selfish!
- 我自私？ - 对，你自私！
Are you fucking kidding me?
你他妈耍我？
Look at yourself!
看看你自己
You're in too deep, man.
你陷进去了，哥们
Yesterday, I found a college application on your desk!
昨天我在你桌子上 找到大学入学申请
I don't know how long this case is going to last.
我不知道这个案子会持续多久
And Eric's going to get into Berkeley, and, honestly, I can get in, too.
艾里克要去伯克利 说实在的，我也能去
Who knows? I could ride this thing out. I could be a doctor or something.
谁知道，也许我能继续升学 也许当博士什么的
Have you lost your fucking mind?
你疯了？
You screwed this investigation all up.
你把这个调查搅得一团糟
At least I know my Miranda rights, you idiot.
至少我知道米兰达警告，笨蛋
You are a very silly man indeed.
你真是个愚蠢的人
Boys, squaws, come quickly.
小伙子、大姑娘，快来啊
Hey! Sorry! It's okay. I'm here.
嗨！对不起！没事了，我来了
I know I missed the first few scenes.
我知道我错过了前面几个场景
I want to thank... Give it up to French Samuels
我想对… 法兰奇萨缪尔斯表示感谢
for ably backing me up. Fuck you, Doug! What?
- 感谢他及时做我的替补 - 去你妈的道格！什么？
I say we just roll right into this thing, huh?
我们正好继续，对吧？
This is my twin. We're together in...
这是我的孪生兄弟，我们一起…
Get the fuck out of here.
你他妈快下台
What are you doing? Have you completely lost your mind?
你在干什么？ 你疯了吗？
What is this?
这是怎么回事？
I don't know, but it's already more exciting.
我不知道，但事情已经越来越刺激了
You're embarrassing me.
你让我好难堪
It's okay. I'll make it up to you.
没事，我会补偿你的
And... Let's fly!
好…飞起来！
- Such bullshit! - Get off of me!
- 什么鬼东西！ - 下去！
I'm not dumb! I'm smart!
我不傻！我很聪明！
You think I'm stupid? You're stupid!
你以为我蠢？你才蠢！
Go, Doug! I guess I should do something.
- 加油，道格！ - 我想我得做点什么了
I should probably not just stand here watching.
我也许不该袖手旁观
I should take action.
我应该行动
Worst best friend ever!
最差的好朋友！
Molly, I'm sorry!
莫莉，对不起！
I don't want to talk to you ever again.
我再也不想理你了！
I'm sorry.
对不起
You stupid idiot!
你个蠢货！
Come here! Come on!
- 过来！ - 来啊！
Make fun of me behind my back and everybody laughs at me?
你在我背后笑话我 还让大家都笑话我，是吧？
I was a loser for four years! You couldn't handle it for five minutes!
我当了四年怂包 你呢，连五分钟都顶不住！
Have some fairy dust, motherfucker!
来点魔粉擦擦吧，混蛋！
Hey, guys, no!
嗨，你们住手！
I heard you call me Rain Man, you asshole!
我听见你们叫我雨人了，王八蛋！
Principal Dadier sucks dick!
迭喋校长舔鸡巴！
You're supposed to be my friend!
你本该是我朋友的！
Stop! Stop it. You're expelled. Both of you are expelled.
住手！住手，你们被开除了 你们俩都被开除了
And that's the end of Act Two.
第二幕结束
Is that it? You're not going to scream at us?
就这些？你不对我们大叫一番？
Nope.
不
I'm gonna just fire you.
我只要解雇你们就行了
Moving out?
搬出去？
Yep.
是
You know what's crazy to me
你知道我哪里犯傻吗？
is that I think that I actually thought that we were brothers.
我真以为我们是兄弟呢
I would've tooken a bullet for you.
我会为你挡子弹
Get in now. Both of you.
上来，马上，你们俩一起
Why should I?
为什么有我？
Just get in the car, man.
上去吧
Get in the fucking car.
他妈给我上车
Nope, not until you ask nicely.
不，不好好说就不上
Please get in the car.
请你上车
Come on, you guys. Come on. Please. Jesus.
快点啊，你们，拜托，上帝
Some messed up shit went down yesterday.
昨天我们交换完东西
Yeah, after we made the exchange,
发生了混乱
our potential business partners got followed by some fucking cops.
我们的未来合作伙伴 被他妈警察跟踪
That's insane, man.
疯了啊，哥们
Are you serious?
真的吗？
Okay, it's just I don't want to go to jail!
好吧，我只是不想进监狱！
You know what happens to a handsome guy like me in jail?
你们知道像我这样的帅哥 进了监狱会怎样吗？
It rhymes with "grape"!
和"房间"押韵的词！
It rhymes with "grape."
和"房间"押韵
I can't let that happen.
我不能让这样的事发生
So I got these from my dad's gun cabinet.
我爸枪柜里的
Eric, Eric, Eric, Eric. Whoa. Come on. Whoa.
- 艾里克，艾里克 - 咳，别这样
Springfield .45s, police issue. Very powerful guns.
春田兵工，45口径，警察用的 非常厉害的枪
You ever use one?
你们用过吗？
We're not really gun people, man. No. No?
- 我们不是玩枪的人，哥们 - 不是？
A lot of things have made me wonder about you.
很多事情让我怀疑你们
Come on.
别这样
Your taste in music.
你对音乐的品味
The fact that you look like a fucking 40-year-old man.
还有你看着像他妈40岁的人
Then after that shit at the play, I realized
直到你们大闹剧场，我才意识到
there's no way you guys could be cops.
你们俩不可能是警察
Yeah, I got this deal going down. The supplier's going to be there.
对，我还有笔生意 供货商会去的
I need people I can trust.
我需要能信任的人
All right. All right, come on.
好了，好了，来吧
Okay, right over here, we're going to shoot these bottles.
来，在那边有些瓶子
We're going to practice, okay? Okay.
- 练下射击，好吗？ - 好
That was... That was actually really fuckin' awesome.
打得真他妈棒啊！
Beginner's luck.
初学者的好运气
All right.
好吧
The supplier wants the deal to go down at prom.
供货商想在毕业舞会上成交
All right, there's going to be all these heavies there,
重量级的大人物都在
but as long as you guys have my back...
但只要你们支持我…
Yeah? Yeah? Shit.
好吗？好吗？
I always got your back.
永远支持你
Time to get our jobs back.
该是我们要回工作的时候了
Let's get ready for prom.
我们准备去舞会吧
Schmidty! Chore time!
施密特！家务活时间！
Mom, we don't have time for chores right now!
妈，我们现在没时间做家务！
If you stay in this house, you have time for chores!
你呆在这房子里 就有时间做家务！
Mom! Ugh!
妈！
Fuck this thing.
他妈的
Here. Huh?
过来
It'll be quicker if I help.
我帮你会快点
There you go.
好了
Thanks.
谢谢
Your shotgun's hanging too low.
你的氰弹枪位置太低了
They're gonna see it.
会被看到的
Thanks.
谢谢
Jenko, uh...
延科
Will you go to prom with me?
可以陪我去舞会吗？
I guess.
我想可以
Are we really going to take down a whole drug operation by ourselves?
凭我们两个就能把整个团伙拿下？
I got some contacts that'll help us.
我有人，到时候会帮我们
กำ I'm lookin' fly
蒂华纳之夜
Brad, what are you doing here? You can't be here.
布莱德，你在这干什么？ 你不能在这里
What if the principal sees you?
校长看见怎么办？
This is wrong, yet so right. What?
- 这是错误，又那么正确 - 什么？
I am so happy you're willing to get in trouble for me.
你们俩为我不怕惹麻烦，我很高兴
You have to go. Please, don't leave me ever.
但你一定要离开，求你了 但永远别离开我
Ms. Griggs, stop. Stop.
格里格丝女士，别说了
Stay! Stay. Stop.
- 留下！留下 - 别说了
What? Stay.
- 什么？ - 留下
Go! Okay.
- 走！ - 好
Stay. Stop. Stop.
- 留下 - 别说了
I'm lost without you. What?
- 没有你我会迷失 - 什么？
Get out of me. I'm going to throw up.
躲远点，我要吐了
You are so hot!
你太迷人了！
All right.
好吧
Hey, pumpkin head.
嗨，南瓜脑袋
I'm very mad at you. Dance with me.
我非常生你的气，陪我跳舞
Are you on that shit? So what if I am?
- 你吸那东西了？ - 那又怎样？
Look, Molly, some serious stuff is about to go down,
听着，莫莉 这里要发生大事
and I don't want you to get hurt.
我不想让你受伤害
I've already been hurt, Doug. I don't care.
我已经受到伤害了，我不在乎了
You need to leave. You need to leave. You need to get out of here right now.
你要离开，离开这里 马上离开
Making a lot of hand gestures!
做很多手势！
Okay, my name's not Doug.
好，我不叫道格
It's Schmidt. What?
- 叫施密特 - 什么？
And I'm a cop. What?
- 我是警察 - 什么？
Okay, and I care about you, and I don't want you to get busted,
好了吧？我很在乎你 我不想让你受伤害
so you have to leave right now.
所以，你现在就离开
Leave the prom right now, Molly.
莫莉，马上离开
I'm serious. Hey. Hey.
- 我说真的 - 嗨，嗨
Penthouse now. Supplier's waiting.
顶楼，供货商等着呢
What are you? Come on. Hey, come on.
- 你是什么？ - 快点，嗨，快点
Supplier's waiting. Is that Eric?
- 供货商等着呢 - 艾里克？
Molly, leave right now. What are you...
- 莫莉，马上离开 - 你说什么…
Just leave right now! What is this?
- 马上离开！ - 怎么回事？
Mr. Walters?
沃尔特斯先生？
Hey!
嗨！
Beautiful Brad, and his brother.
帅哥布莱德，和他的弟弟
Wow. You look great.
哇，这身打扮真帅
You're the supplier? You're a teacher.
你是供货商？你是老师啊
And I was stuck on a teacher's salary, bro.
我让老师的工资卡住了，兄弟
Could barely pay my alimony. What are you gonna do? Ha!
几乎不够生活费 换了你，你会怎么办？
Oh, yeah.
啊，是啊
You boys are so good at this.
你们男孩子这方面太强了
Oh, yeah, Cinnamon!
哦，好啊，肉桂！
Oh, my God, we're getting such good evidence.
天，我们收集了这么好的证据
I stole some of that Bunsen burner crap
我从化学实验室偷了点
from the chem lab, threw in some of my Cool Deets,
破煤气喷灯 扔点我自己的清凉型立体脆进去
and it was muy delicioso!
就特别可口了！
Then one day I catch Eco Butt-munch over here
有一天，我在这看见环保宝贝 艾里克
smoking a J.J. behind the field house,
在更衣室里吸大麻香烟
and I'm like, "Hey, you want to make some coin?"
我说 "嗨，你想赚点钱吗？"
What a green penis that guy is, huh?
他真环保啊，连小弟弟都是绿色的
There's my quesadilla.
我的玉米薄饼来了
I hurt my hands!
我伤了手！
Bitch.
妹子
Oh, shit.
该死
You guys look crazy scary.
你们真胆小
How many of you are there?
你们有多少人？
A lot.
很多
Karl.
卡尔
Patch looks pimp, man.
眼罩挺合适啊
Thank you.
谢谢
He's gonna recognize us, man.
他会认出我们的
I'm freaking out.
我吓死了
This is Walters, he made the stuff.
这是沃尔特斯，东西是他做的
Real pleasure to meet you. Fuck what his name is.
- 见到你很高兴 - 妈的，不管他是谁
Your shit's good.
你的货不错
Thank you.
谢谢 你说出这话，分量就不轻了
That means a lot coming from you. What, you having a party now?
你们正开舞会？
Who are these two motherfuckers?
这两个混蛋是谁？
Fuck!
靠！
Hey. Hey. How's it going?
- 嗨 - 嗨，你好啊
Nah, nah, it's cool, man, they're my boys, so...
不不，挺酷，哥们 他们是我的人…
Are they? Yeah.
- 是吗？ - 是
I don't like strangers.
我不喜欢陌生人
How do you ever expect to make any new friends with that attitude?
这种态度怎么交新朋友？
It's, like, everyone's a stranger till you give them a chance, man.
你不给机会 人人都是陌生的
What the fuck are you talking about?
你他妈在说什么？
I don't even...
我甚至连…
Just fuckin' around.
乱说而已啦
Do your thing, man. Proceed.
做事吧，继续做你的事
Hey, kid, come here.
嗨，孩子，过来
You, you look familiar.
你，你看上去眼熟
Me? Yeah.
- 我？ - 是
I was in a French fry commercial when I was a kid,
我小时候上过炸土豆条的广告
so people are like, you know, often say, "Oh, I think I know you,"
所以人们总是说"我想我认识你"
but I don't think we've ever met before.
但我想我们以前没见过
Do I look like I eat French fries?
我看着像喜欢吃土豆条的吗？
I don't know, you look like you're in great shape,
你不像，你身材保持得很棒
but maybe you have, like, one cheat day, like a carb blowout, you know? I don't know.
也许，你有某一天给自己放松一下 大吃一顿，我不知道
Nah.
不会
Yeah, the theme song was, like...
对，主题歌是这样的…
กำ Come to Andrew's French Fry Emporium
快来安德鲁的炸薯条中心
กำ Where friendship and French fries
这里友谊和薯条
กำ Go hand in hand กำ
手拉手，肩并肩
That's my quesadilla!
那是我的玉米片
Who wants a piece? Huh?
谁想来一片，啊？
I know you're in there, Doug, or whatever your name is!
我知道你在，道格 不管你叫什么
You lied to me!
你跟我撒谎！
I'm gonna kill you, you stupid fucking cop!
我要杀了你 你他妈的笨蛋警察！
Hey, you guys, she just called me a stupid fucking cock. That's rude.
嗨，大伙听明白 她骂我是他妈的笨蛋公鸡
Dickhead narc motherfucker!
你个猪头探警混蛋！
Did she just say "nickhead dark motherfucker"?
她刚说 "黑尼克头谈情混蛋"？
That's just racist.
种族歧视
I know these two.
我认识他们俩
Your boys are cops! They're cops!
你的人是警察！他们是警察！
Police! Get on the ground!
警察！趴地上！
You get on the fuckin' ground!
你俩给我趴地上！
We asked you first! I don't give a damn!
- 我们先说的！ - 我不管！
You're fucking cops?
你们他妈的是条子？
But we partied together, man.
可我们一起聚会来着
You bought us Taco Bell.
你给我们买的塔克贝尔快餐
Eric, honestly, that was a sincere gesture.
艾里克，那是很真诚的举动
You made me this friendship bracelet.
你给我做的这个友谊手链
Well, he's not really your friend. He was pretending the whole time.
他不是真朋友 他一直都在伪装
I'm gonna cut this the fuck off later, all right?
我回头一定把手链剪断，好吧？
What the fuck is going on?
这是他妈的干什么？
Shut this kid up!
这孩子闭嘴！
Him, too. No, no! Hey, wait!
- 还有他 - 不不，嗨，等等
No, no, no. Listen, I'm with you guys!
不不，我是你们的人
I didn't know these guys were cops!
不知道他们是警察
I'm getting out of here.
我离开这
I fucking hate you!
我他妈恨死你了！
Get that out of my face!
把手拿开！
Molly! Oh, there you are!
- 莫莉！ - 啊，你在那！
What the fuck!
怎么回事！
Drop your guns, or I'll spray her brains all over the room!
放下枪，不然我蹦了她！
Trying to take a hostage, some goddamn TV show shit?
学会挟持人质了 都他妈电视里看来的
I don't know! I'm trying to help, all right? I've never done this shit before.
我不知道，我是想帮忙 以前从没干过
Well, you're fucking up.
都让你搅了
Drop the guns or she's dead! She looks dead already.
- 放下枪，否则杀了她 - 她好像已经死了
What? No.
什么？不
Oh, Jesus.
天
Yeah, I can hear her breathing.
我能听见她呼吸
She just passed out from the drugs. We're good.
药物作用昏过去了 我们没事
Drop the guns or...
放下枪，否则…
All right, all right, just chill out.
好吧，好吧，冷静点
We're gonna drop our guns.
我们放下枪
You got to let the kids go, and no one's gonna die, okay?
你放了两个孩子 不要有人送命，好吧？
Just drop the guns, and kick them over here.
放下枪，踢过来
D.B., shoot these motherfuckers.
D.B. 把这两混蛋给我杀了
Oh, come on, that's unfair! We put our guns down in good faith.
怎么这样啊，这不公平 我们讲诚信，放下了枪
You're a liar, and you're mean!
你是个骗子，小人！
That's unfair. We're all friends here.
- 不公平 - 我们都是朋友
Let's just relax, and we can all leave here as friends.
- 我们大家都放松点 - 大家离开，不伤和气
Yeah, let's do that. Y'all boys are stupid.
- 好，干吧 - 你们都是蠢货
Oh, my God, we're gonna die. We're gonna die.
哦，天，我们死定了 死定了
God damn it!
该死的！
Tom Hanson, DEA! On your knees!
汤姆汉森，缉毒局，都跪下！
What the fuck?
娘的，怎么？
Now! Fuck!
- 立刻！ - 靠！
Doug Penhall, DEA! You're under arrest!
道格潘浩，缉毒局的！你们被逮捕了！
Guns down, all of you! Domingo, tell them!
放下武器，你们全体！多明戈，告诉他们
Put them down.
放下吧
Nice! Yes!
好！太棒了！
Shut the fuck up!
他妈的闭嘴！
You little dweebs just ruined a five-year investigation.
你们两个小白痴 刚刚毁了五年的调查
We had no idea.
我们一无所知
You're, like, an amazing actor, man.
你就像超级演员
You played saxophone at my sister's wedding, man!
我妹妹婚礼上 你还吹过萨克斯呢！
Tough titty. I fucked her, too.
真糟糕，我还睡了她
What?
什么？
You little turds.
你们两个讨厌鬼
Do you have any idea how difficult it is to infiltrate a gang like this?
你们知道 打入这样的黑帮有多困难吗？
Do you see this nose?
看见这个鼻子吗？
That is a fake nose.
这是假的
Do you want to wear a fake nose on your fuckin' head
你愿意在脸上戴个假鼻子吗？
for, like, months on end? Glue and shit?
成年累月地，还得用胶粘
Worse things in the world.
世上最难过的事
We had to get fuckin' tattoos on our dicks, man.
我们还得他妈的在阳物上刺青
Hey, actually, I just said that
嗨，其实，我刚才
to mess with you. What?
- 跟你搅和的 - 什么？
Looks tough.
看着像硬汉
Look, we know what it's like being undercover.
我们知道卧底的滋味
Metro Police, Jump Street Division.
城市警察，跳跳街分部
Come on, you guys are Jump Street?
你们是跳跳街的？
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- 对 - 对
That's funny, because we were actually Jump Street.
有意思哈，我们实际上也是跳跳街的
What? Yeah. Oh, yeah.
- 什么？ - 对
Oh, shit!
哦，该死
Oh, my God! Oh, shit.
- 啊，天啊！ - 该死
Oh, my God, dude!
哦，天啊！
Get them!
拿下他们！
Motherfucker!
混蛋！
Shoot them!
开枪！
Fuck that.
他妈的
That was a gun.
是枪声
Somebody definitely got shot.
肯定有人被打死了
All right.
好了
Here, take the money, all right? We're getting out of here.
这，拿着钱，好吗？ 我们离开这
Did I hit anything?
我打中了吗？
You were shooting at the fuckin' ceiling.
你他妈冲着房顶开枪
Doug.
道格
I know sometimes I was a jerk to you
我知道一起卧底的时候
when we were undercover.
有时你觉得我是个怪人
It's just... I didn't feel good about myself.
只是…我的自我感觉不好
All that stuff I wore, like the bracelets, the rings, the tight pants,
我所有的穿戴 手链、戒指、紧身裤
was just so
只是为了
that people would think I'm cool.
让人们觉得我酷
The only approval
我需要的
that I ever needed
唯一赞许
was my best friend.
是我最好的朋友
Thanks, man.
谢谢，兄弟
The money's gone!
钱已经转移了！
Come on, let's roll.
大伙，撤！
We gotta get out of here, man.
我们得赶快离开这
Are you telling me it's on?
你是说我们开始？
Let's do this. Let's make a baby.
- 咱们干吧 - 我们造个孩子
What? What are you talking about? I don't know.
- 你说什么？ - 不知道
I was trying to sound cool. Sorry.
我只是想扮酷，对不起
That was crazy! You killed a guy!
你疯了！你杀了一个人！
Oh, fuckin' shit!
哦，他妈的！
Hey, hey, we'll lose them in the prom! Go!
嗨，到舞会上把他们甩开！快！
Go, go, go, go!
快快快！
Where'd they go?
他们去哪了？
Molly!
莫莉！
Shit!
妈的！
You want to drive? Yeah, I do, actually.
- 你想开车吗？ - 我想
Okay, cool.
好，酷
Nice! Did it look cool when I did it?
- 漂亮！ - 我刚才酷吗？
That's what I'm talking about! Yeah!
- 我说的就是这个！ - 酷！
How you guys doing back there, huh?
你们在后面怎么样啊？
God, I love high school!
上帝，我爱高中！
Best prom night ever!
最棒的舞会之夜！
Shoot them! Stay on them!
- 开枪！ - 跟紧了！
I'm on them! I'm on them!
我跟得很紧！很紧！
Oh, good, you guys, come hang out with me back here.
啊，好啊 你们到后面来跟我玩啊
Oh, fuck, dude. Lisa, what are you doing? Did she pass out back there?
- 哦该死，丽萨，在干嘛？ - 她在后面晕过去了？
Hey, you got a gun. Why don't you shoot back there?
嗨，你也有枪 为什么不在后面打他们？
Shoot that gun, shoot that gun!
开枪啊，开枪！
All right, one second!
好的，等一下
Just shoot someone, you bitch!
打啊，你个妹子
Peek-a-boo!
露个头！
Give me my money!
把钱给我！
Fuck that! Fuck that! No! No!
去他妈的！这样不行！不行！
I can't do this! I'm supposed to go to Berkeley!
我做不到！ 我本来该去伯克利的！
I'm gonna get the party started!
我要启动聚会
I'm gonna get the party started! No! No! Lisa, no!
- 我要启动聚会 - 不！丽萨，不！
Hey, I'm living my dream of standing in a limo!
我站在豪华轿车上的梦想 实现了！
What?
什么？
You're killing my dream! Come in.
- 你扼杀了我的梦！ - 进来
What? I'm trying to party. Down!
- 什么？我想参加聚会 - 下来！
Bitch!
妹子！
What? Fuck!
什么？靠！
I'll kill you!
我要杀了你！
Kill you!
杀了你！
No! No! Stay where you are.
- 不不！ - 呆在那别动
Go! Go, go!
快！快走！
No! Stop!
不！停住！
I'm not fucking kidding! Look, I'm trying to shoot people!
我他妈没开玩笑 听着，我要开枪射击
Will you stop! Just for two seconds!
你别说了！就两秒钟！
You're really hot and you're really slutty and it's awesome,
你很性感，很浪 真的很好
but I got to shoot people right now!
但我现在得开枪
You think I'm hot?
你觉得我性感？
I wanna... Oh, my God!
我要…啊，天啊！
Wait, guys! Call me!
等等！打电话给我！
Let me know where you're ending up later.
告诉我你们最后在哪里
I'm almost out of ammo.
我快没子弹了
We're fucked.
我们完蛋了
Give me my money!
把钱给我！
I got an idea.
我有个主意
You still got those shotgun shells? Yeah.
- 你还有子弹壳吧？ - 有
Pop Quiznos.
抽查小测验
What do you get when lithium batteries react to potassium nitrate?
锉电池和硝酸钾反应 产生什么？
That would be a covalent bond, brother.
共价键，兄弟
That's when two atoms, they share electrons.
那是两个原子，共享电子
You see, they both need what the other one has.
你看，他们彼此都需要对方的电子
That makes them stick together.
这样他们能紧密团结
Are you saying we're covalent bonds?
你是说我们是共价键？
What? No.
什么？不
We're not atoms, dude.
我们不是原子，伙计
What's this? Tequila?
- 这是什么？ - 龙舌兰酒
I don't know, it was supposed to explode.
我不知道，应该能爆炸
Oh, shit!
哦，妈的！
Where'd you learn how to do that, man?
你从哪学来的？
App chemistry, bitch.
大学先求化学
Come on, blondie.
过来，金发妞
Molly!
莫莉！
Drop your weapon!
放下武器！
Don't you fuckin' pull that arm up.
你他妈敢举胳膊？！
Don't.
别动
Oh-ho! Looks like you're out of ammo, asshole!
好像你没子弹了，混蛋！
Come on! Get out here!
过来！下车！
What? What's going on? All right.
- 怎么回事？ - 好了
All right, here's the deal. Nobody moves, or she's gonna get hurt.
好吧，这样 谁都不许动，不然她倒霉
Do you understand? Nobody move!
明白吗？谁都不许动！
All right. Eric, help me.
- 好 - 艾里克，救救我
Don't you have a gun?
你没枪？
All right, don't move!
好的，别动！
Come on, let's go. Let's go. No!
- 来，咱们走，咱走 - 不！
Hey! Hey, hey! Hey, no, no, I said don't move!
- 嗨嗨嗨！ - 嗨，不，我说的不许动！
Oh, fuck, you shot him! Oh, God!
- 哦，妈的，你打中他了！ - 哦，天啊！
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
You shot my partner, you motherfucker!
你打中我搭档了，混蛋！
I didn't mean to shoot you! I meant to shoot him!
我没打算打你！ 我是想打他的！
Are you alive, buddy? You okay? You took a bullet for me, man.
你还活着吗，哥们？没事吧？ 你为我挡了子弹
Yeah, I'm feeling a little ambivalent about that right now.
嗯，对此我现在感觉很矛盾
Didn't you hear me? I said don't move! I said that! You heard, right?
没听见我说不许动吗？ 我说了，你也听见了，对吗？
Eric, you heard me!
艾里克，你听见了
- I said don't move! - Eric, help me!
- 我说不许动！ - 艾里克，救救我！
- You got this. - Hey, hold still.
- 你能行 - 嗨，别动
Freeze!
站住！
Shoot!
开枪！
Come on.
开啊
You peaked in high school, motherfucker.
你的好日子该结束了，混蛋
Oh, shit.
啊，妈的
I shot him in the dick.
我打中了他的
You shot me in the dick!
你打中了我的牛
Oh, my God!
啊，天啊！
Yes!
太棒了！
You are under arrest!
你被逮捕了！
It definitely came out my asshole! You have the right to remain silent!
- 子弹肯定从屁眼出去了 - 你有权利保持沉默
Anything you say can and will be used against you
你所说的一切 都可能用作法庭控告你的
in a court of law!
证据！
You have the right to an attorney!
你有权利请律师
If you cannot afford an attorney, one will be appointed for you!
如果你付不起律师费 法庭会为你指派一名！
Do you understand these rights as they have been read to you?
你是否完全了解你的上述权利呢？
Fuck you! Bitch!
去你妈的！妹子！
Yes! Yes!
好啊！好啊！
We did it, man!
我们成功了！
We did it.
我们成功了
God, I feel so good.
天，我感觉太好了
We did it, man!
我们成功了！
You're a goddamn rock star.
你是他妈的大摇滚明星了
Do you feel that?
感觉到了吗？
God damn, you're so cool.
妈的，你太酷了
You just shot him in the dick.
正好打中他的
I've never seen that. Who does that?
我从来没见过，谁打中过？
Look, I'm sorry I called you Rain Man.
叫你雨人，我很抱歉
I know I didn't say you were, but you're smart.
我知道，我是说你就是 但你很聪明
You're a smart guy, and you're thoughtful,
你是个聪明的人，考虑周全
and you're sincere and you're sweet and you're loyal...
真诚、和蔼、忠实…
And I fuckin' cherish you.
我他妈太稀罕你了
Should we high-five?
能击掌吗？
Ow! My hand!
我的手！
Are you all right? Should we get you to the hospital, man?
你没事吗？ 我把你送医院吧？
Yeah, I think we need to call somebody. Hey, call somebody!
- 好，得找人来帮忙 - 嗨，叫人！
I got to get my dick sewn back on.
我得把欧旎厝
You shut the fuck up. Hey, you shut up.
- 你他妈闭嘴 - 嗨，你闭嘴
That's not funny. Is that it?
- 这可不好玩 - 这个是吗？
What?
什么？
That's my dick!
那是我的牛
Pick up my dick! Please!
捡起来！求你！
No, we're not picking up your dick.
没门，我们不会捡的
Fuckin' pick my dick up!
他妈的我来捡
Oh, fuck!
啊，他妈的
He's my friend.
他是我朋友
They don't serve vegan in jail, bitch.
监狱里没有素食，妹子
Hey.
嗨
Molly...
莫莉…
I'm really sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I know you wanted a guy to trust, and I wanted to be that person so badly.
我知道你需要一个值得信赖的人 我也非常想做这个人
And I let you down in a lot of ways.
但，我很多地方都让你失望
And...
而且…
It's good that you're mad at me.
你对我恼火，这很好
I think it's good. I think you should be mad at more guys,
我想这很好 你应该跟更多的人发火
because you deserve a guy who's good and who doesn't lie to you.
因为，你应该得到一个对你好 而且不撒谎的人
And you should never settle for less than that.
找不到这样的人 就坚决不嫁
There are good guys out there
世界上还是有很多好人的
who aren't assholes like me.
不像我，是个混蛋
Thanks for saving my life,
谢谢你救了我的命
asshole.
混蛋
Put her there, partner.
握手为证，搭档
I'll come back later.
我一会再来
We're, like, in the end of Die Hard right now, but it's our actual life.
我们有点像Die Hard的结尾 但我们是真实生活
It's crazy.
疯狂的
Number one or two? Three.
- 第一集还是第二集？ - 第三集
Sam Jackson one. Yeah! Sam Jackson style.
- 塞米尔杰克逊的，对！ - 他的风格
Boom, motherfuckers! What's going on? Come on!
轰！混蛋们！ 一切都好吗？来啊！
Where is he? There's my guy!
他在哪？他在这！
There he is! That's him. That's him.
在这！就是他，就是他
Enough. Too long on the hug.
- 行了 - 抱得太长了
Congratulations, you crazy, sick, vigilante motherfuckers.
祝贺你们，两个疯狂的 有病的、义务混蛋警员
You got your first arrest, huh?
你终于完成了第一次逮捕哈？
- Look. Got something made for you. - You didn't!
- 看，做了个东西给你 - 不会吧！
Come on. All right, all right. Enough. Enough.
- 来，好吧，好吧 - 够了，够了
New assignment.
新任务
Since you two cowboys love to drink booze,
你们两个牛仔既然喜欢豪饮
smoke weed with kids, and fuck anything with a big ass in jeans
跟年轻人一起抽点大麻 还喜欢泡妞
with low self-esteem,
尤其是没多少自尊的
I'm gonna send you to a place where all that shit is allowed.
我将把你们两派往 这一切都被允许的地方
Oh, I love Disneyland!
我喜欢迪士尼乐园！
You two sons of bitches are going to college!
你们两个妹子养的 去给我上大学！
No! Yes!
- 太好了！ - 不好！
Boo-yah!
嘘！
Oh, my God! You're like two Hardy Boys in one!
啊，天啊！ 你像两个猛男合二为一！
Oh, fuck!
啊，靠！
Hey, why are you here, Scott?
斯格特，你来这干什么？
What, Kennedy High isn't having any parties tonight?
肯尼迪中学今晚没有聚会？